（里约热内卢）
我认为女人可以做任何事情
I think women can do anything.
我觉得 即使她们有能力去做
Well, I mean, just because they can,
但这不代表着她们应该做 对吧
doesn't mean they should, right?
试想一下女人修车
Think about women fixing cars,
开计程车
driving a taxi,
砌墙
installing some drywall.
- 有何不可呢 - 不
- Why not? - No.
相信我
Look, trust me.
像你这样的女孩子 你不会想干这些事的
A girl like you, you don't really want this.
- 像我这样的女孩子 - 嗯哼
- A girl like me? - Mm-hm.
我是说 我会对一切事敞开大门
I mean, I want all my options available.
这样我就可以选择自己的路
so I can decide for myself.
啊 独立小姐
Ah, Miss Independent.
我就说嘛
That's right.
- 这就是我 - 我喜欢
- That's me. - I love it.
过来
Come here.
只不过你现在坐在这儿
Except you're sitting here,
吃着我的食物 看我的景色
eating my food, enjoying my view.
这是我的选择
By choice.
我选择你陪着我
Mm, I chose you to join me.
是我选择引起你的注意
I chose to make you notice me.
那不是你的选择 萨比娜
That is not your choice, Sabina.
那是上帝给你的礼物
That is God's gift to you.
天啊
Gosh…
但你不觉得收到礼物之后
But don't you think it's sort of.
怎么处理才是重要的事吗
what you do with those gifts that really matters?
人人都这样
Every one of us.
男人 女人
Men, women.
我们只想充分发挥自己的潜能
We all just wanna fulfill our potential,
随心所欲地生活而已
live our heart's desires.
那就是我想要的生活
That's the kind of world I wanna live in.
我的生活呢 是百万傍身
Well, my world is me making millions.
你在侧
with you by my side.
但是我擅长的事情太多了
It's just that I'm so good at so many things.
- 哦 是吗 - 是啊
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
比如什么
Like what?
比如
Well…
我的工作
At my job,
就很大程度地利用了女人的优势
it's actually considered a huge advantage to be a woman.
是啊 如果你很漂亮的话
Yeah, if you're beautiful,
别人对你就不会有其他要求
nothing else is really expected of you.
但如果你不好看
And if you're not,
那基本上就没什么存在感
you're pretty much rendered invisible.
在我们这一行
And in my line of work,
没存在感 不被期待
invisibility, low expectations…
这可都是优势
they come in very handy.
听起来像家庭主妇
Housewife, sounds like.
做家庭主妇没什么不好的
Nothing wrong with being a housewife.
只不过那不是我的选择
Just not my choice.
- 我不会讲葡萄牙语 - 我知道
- I don't speak Portuguese. - I know.
没错 就是这样
Yeah, that's it.
- 你知不知道 - 什么
- Did you know… - What?
男人需要多花7秒钟的时间
That it takes men an additional seven seconds.
才能察觉到一个女人对他有威胁
to perceive a woman as a threat compared to a man.
刺激吗
Isn't that wild?
- 你是谁 - 谁 我吗
- Who are you? - Who, me?
我只是个诱饵 蠢货
I'm just the decoy, stud.
- 多少人 - 九个
- How many? - Nine!
全体行动
Send the lot.
让你偷女人小孩和难民的救济金
You stole aid money from women and children and refugees!
那叫盗用公款
It's called embezzlement!
盗用公款 这词真高级啊
"Embezzlement"? That's fancy.
- 你肯定就是会计了 - 你是谁
- You must be the accountant. - Who are you?
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
宝贝 你右滑了对吧
Oh, baby, baby, you swiped right!
我现在是你女朋友了
I'm your girlfriend now!
底层所有东西的都装 开始吧
Everything on the bottom row. Let's go.
你不是干这行的料 我建议你转行
You're not cut out for this. I recommend a new line of work.
波士利
Bosley!
晚上好 天使们
Evening, Angels.
情况看起来不错啊
Well, all this looks very promising.
非常出色
Outstanding.
但澳洲乔尼在哪儿呢
But what about Australian Jonny?
嗒哒
Ta-da!
- 你一定会后悔的 - 行吧
- Oh, you're gonna regret this. - Yeah.
我本来打算给你整个世界的
I was gonna give you the world.
问题是 你话太多了
The thing is, is you just talk way too much.
你超级粘人 又那么猴急
You're super clingy and come on way too strong.
你是我见过的
You are the most incredible woman.
- 最与众不同的女人 - 我知道
- I've ever met. - I know.
这就是耗时四个月的侦查 跨两国的追踪
So that's four months' surveillance, two countries.
还是我这辈子经历过最尴尬的约会
and the most embarrassing date I have ever been on in my life.
- 没问题了吧 - 我会把他
- Are we good? - I will address this.
还有在场的这些新朋友们
to the U.S. Justice Department,
一起交给美国司法部
along with, uh, all your new friends here.
- 我们可以走了 - 太棒了
- We're good to go. - Sweet.
天啊 我得赶紧离开这儿 休一个星期的假
I'm out of here, man. I'm gonna take a week off,
去泰国沙滩狂欢
party my ass off on a Thai beach.
简 你也该试试
Jane, you should give it a shot:
去海边 找个人娱乐一下你的
beaches, letting someone play with your, uh…
我有自己的娱乐方式
I have fun in my own ways.
好吧
Oh. Cool.
你晚上在家擦剑吗
You sharpen your samurai swords at night?
还是扮演猫女
Cosplay Catwoman?
我倒是真的愿意买票观赏
I'd actually pay to see that.
晚上偶尔吃点麸质你就会觉得
Occasionally eat gluten at night and feel…
这就挺娱乐的
That was fun.
她们是谁
So who were they?
你刚刚见到的是天使们
You were in the presence of Angels.
问题是 乔尼
But the question is, Jonny…
你是谁
who are you?
《霹雳娇娃》
（汉堡）
（一年后）
嘿 英格丽德
Hey, Ingrid.
你迟到了 弗莱明先生在等你了
You are late. Mr. Fleming is waiting.
不是9点开会吗
Oh, wasn't the meeting set for 9?
是的 会议是在9点开始
Yes, 9 a.M. Is when the meeting starts,
现在就是9点了
which is exactly now.
你跟布洛克先生相处过吗
Have you ever spent time with him? Mr. Brok?
没 当然没有
No, of course not.
他邀请过我去过
He had me over to his chateau,
他法国的庄园
which is in France.
我们坐在那儿 然后我问他
And we were sitting there, and I'm asking him,
我说 布洛克先生 你听说过汉弗莱·戴维吗
I said, "Mr. Brok, have you ever heard of Humphry Davy?"
他说 没有
And he says, "No."
我说 那你听说过约瑟夫·斯旺
I say, "Have you ever heard of Joseph Swan.
或者是亚历山大·洛迪金吗 没听过
or Alexander Lodygin?" "No clue."
然后我说 好吧
So I say, "Okay.
那托马斯·爱迪生呢
Uh, what about Thomas Edison?"
当然了 谁不知道呢 他发明了灯泡
"Well, of course. Who hasn't? He invented the light bulb."
是吧 但你猜怎么着
Right? But guess what?
另外三个人也发明了灯泡
So did those other three guys.
还是在爱迪生之前
Before Edison.
但爱迪生是第一个将灯泡推向市场的人
But Edison was first to market.
你明白我的意思了吗
Do you see my point?
我们有一个将要
We have a product that will.
在能源行业掀起革命的产品
revolutionize the power industry.
但我们必须是首个将它推向市场的人
But we have to be first.
就是现在
The time is now.
我就是这么告诉布洛克先生的 他也同意了
And that's what I told Mr. Brok, and he agrees with me.
显然是这样
Obviously.
- 我 - 埃琳娜 谢谢你过来一趟
- I… - Elena, thank you for coming in.
我跟你聊得很开心
I love how this conversation went.
准确来说 我什么话都还没说
Technically, I haven't said anything.
我们就不要在谁说了什么这个问题上纠结了
Let's not get caught in a game of who said what.
弗莱明先生 我知道克里斯托有多重要 好吗
Mr. Fleming, I know how important Calisto is, okay?
我是主程序设计师 它就是我的孩子
I'm the lead programmer on it. It's my baby.
- 没错 - 但我在报告中写了
- Yeah. - But as I wrote in my report,
现在它的谐波范围
right now there is a possibility.
有可能会颠倒
for the harmonic range to be reversed.
我们都知道那会有多危险
We both know how dangerous that could be.
你不知道我知道什么
Well, I mean, you don't know what I know. Heh.
你知道胡里奥 那个二级工程师
Y-you know Julio? The second engineer?
他因为脑中风现在还在住院中
He's actually still in hospital after a brain seizure,
仅仅就因为在一次测试中暴露了而已
and he was only partially exposed during a test.
那是推测 是推测
Allegedly. Allegedly.
胡里奥是个笨蛋
And Julio was an idiot.
我只是想要根权限
All I need is root access.
和永久修复区块链瑕疵的
and time to permanently fix the flaw.
时间而已 让它稳定安全
in the blockchain so it will stay safe…
英格丽德 帮我倒杯卡布奇诺
Ingrid, can I get a cappuccino?
好了 我看了你的报告了
Okay. I read your report.
我也让其他领导看过你的报告了
I've had others read your report.
我们就是不同意你的要求而已
We just simply disagree with you.
布洛克先生看过我的报告了吗 我想如果他看过了
Has Mr. Brok read my report? I think that if he read…
让我把话说清楚吧
Let me be crystal clear here.
我们已经开发了克里斯托五年了
We have developed Calisto for five years,
我们就要把它推向市场了
and we are going to market.
它是安全的 完善的
It is safe and it is ready,
我们也会这样汇报给布洛克先生的
and that's what we're telling Mr. Brok.
你什么都不准跟布洛克先生说
And you are telling Mr. Brok nothing.
听着 埃琳娜 你是个聪明人
Look, Elena, you're much too smart.
该知道适可而止的 不是吗
to keep pushing this forward, aren't you?
很好
Good.
- 我知道汉弗莱·戴维是谁 - 那你很棒
- I knew who Humphry Davy was. - Good for you.
- 你东西掉了 - 噢 不 这不是我的
- You dropped something. - Oh, no. That's not mine.
我从不乱扔杂物的 所以肯定是你的
Well, I don't litter, so it must be yours.
你可能会需要它
You might need it.
（汤森德机构）
（洛杉矶）
波士利 001号
Bosley, 001.
（欢迎你 波士利）
你个怪老头 你真以为
You old codger. You really thought.
我们会让你这样静悄悄地离开吗
we were gonna let you just sneak away quietly?
你不必如此
You didn't have to.
不仅是我
It's not just me.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
- 嘿 你好 - 早上好 先生
- Hey! Bonjour. - Buenos días, se?or.
- 早上好 - 大家都在呢
- Buenos días. - Gang's all here.
我们想要祝你退休快乐
We all wanted to wish you a happy retirement.
谢谢你 波士利
Thank you, Bosley.
- 还有你 先生 - 波士利
- And you, sir. - Bosley.
波士利 谢谢你
Bosley. Thank you.
- 你 - 你的辉煌事迹太多了
- You! - You've had one hell of a run.
值得大肆庆祝一番
It deserves to be celebrated.
我甚至还做了一个回忆片段
I even put together a little walk down memory lane.
- 一起看看吧 - 别 别
- Shall we? Ha, ha! - Oh, no, no.
开始喽
Here it comes.
校草啊 哈哈
Oh, yeah! Ha, ha!
- 刚从牛津毕业时的样子 - 帅啊
- Fresh-faced Oxford graduate. - Yeah!
- 天呐 - 这照片我找了很久呢 瞧瞧这照片
- Oh, Lord. - I dug deep for this. Look at that.
我可是本色出演
That's not a disguise.
显然你那些年过得很开心啊
You clearly had a lot of fun over the years.
你知道的 那些日子很美好
You know, life was good in those days.
那套西装你从哪儿找来的
Where did you get that suit?
蒙特卡洛
Monte Carlo.
还真给我找到了 那就是证据
It really happened. There's the proof.
当你开设了欧洲分部
Well, when you opened the European offices,
汤森德事务所便进入国际化时代
you took the Townsend Agency international.
没有你 就没有今天的我们
None of us would be here without you.
- 是的 - 特别是我 谢谢你
- Yes. - Especially me. Thank you.
我非常感动 谢谢你 谢谢你们
Well, I'm very touched. Thank you. All of you.
说两句吧 快 致词 波士利 致词
Say a few words. Come on, speech, Bosley. Speech!
- 别了吧 - 致词 致词 致词
- Oh, no. - Speech, speech, speech!
致词 致词 致词
Speech, speech, speech!
老实说 我真的受宠若惊
Well, frankly, I am overwhelmed.
我很感激
I'm grateful…
这些年我们共同的努力
for all the work that we have done together.
你们知道的 那时查理还不确定
And, you know, Charlie wasn't sure.
我们可以复制他在加州
that we could replicate the success.
取得的成就
that he had here in California.
- 但我们做到了 - 没错
- But we made it work… - That's right.
在这个世界还没准备好接受天使的时候
…in a world that was really not ready for the Angels.
整整40年
For 40 years,
我招聘她们 训练她们
I recruited them, I trained them…
我以她们为骄傲
and I'm so very proud of them.
波士利们
Bosleys…
- 你们要保护她们的安全 - 会的
- you keep them safe. - Will do.
- 收到 收到 - 我们会的 我的朋友
- Hear, hear. - We will, my friend.
而我 就像查理说的
And so for me, as Charlie said,
是时候华丽退场了
time to make an exit stage left.
等等 说到查理
Wha… Ah, speaking of Charlie…
你好 波士利
Hello, Bosley.
你好 查理
Hello, Charlie.
看看你身处的这个房间 老朋友
If you look around this room, old friend,
你眼前的这些男士女士们
you'll see the men and women.
他们会带着你的成就继续辉煌
who will carry your legacy into the future.
你的领导精神和奉献精神是无与伦比的
Your leadership and commitment is unparalleled.
你给予我们的 是我们还不清的恩情
We owe you a debt we cannot repay.
因此 我们给你准备了块手表
So instead, we got you a watch.
- 手表 - 是的
- A watch? - Yes.
谢谢你 查理
Thank you, Charlie.
退休快乐
Enjoy your retirement.
这是你应得的
You deserve it.
干杯
A toast!
你真的很喜欢开派对
You really like to party.
这样白天才能喝酒嘛 这才是我的心头好
It's the day drinking. That's what I like the most.
你也不赖嘛
You're not bad either.
敬波士利
To Bosley.
- 敬波士利 - 敬大家
- To Bosley! - To all of you.
我要说的就是我所唱的 我觉得这很重要
This speech is my recital I think it's very vital.
摇滚的秘诀就在于踩点正确 但这很难
To rock a rhyme, that's right On time, "It's Tricky" Is…
谢谢你 就这样 你赶紧走吧 他来了
Thank you. That's it. Please move. He's coming.
- 好的 - 准备好了吗 谢谢你
- For sure. - Are we ready? Thank you.
说唱很溜啊 兄弟
That was a sick flow, bro.
- 别说了 - 你还真唱啊
- Oh, shut up, shut up. - You really went for it.
那边有两个位置
There's two seats over there.
- 很难 - 太难了
- It's tricky. - Tricky.
- 太难了 - 太太难了
- Tricky. - Tricky.
兰斯顿 闭嘴
Langston, shut up.
掌声有请我们的创始人
Everyone, please help me welcome our founder,
我们的投资方 亚历山大·布洛克
our benefactor, Alexander Brok.
布洛克先生 您定下了
Mr. Brok, you have set.
创新的最高标准
the highest standards for innovation.
我相信 我 在团队的小小帮助下
I believe that I, along with a little help from my team,
已经完成了挑战
have met that challenge.
今天 在我带领下 汉堡能源公司将
Today, I instructed the Hamburg power utility.
这栋建筑从电网中独立开来
to disconnect this building from the electrical grid.
但我们完全不会没电可用
But we are far from powerless.
布洛克先生
Mr. Brok,
请您授予根权限 可以吗
would you grant us root access?
你好 亚历山大
Hello, Alexander.
根权限确认
Root access granted.
克里斯托 开灯
Calisto, turn on the lights.
克里斯托 匹配姐妹装置
Calisto, pair with sister devices.
克里斯托 电力全开
Calisto, full power.
布洛克工业供电全球
Brok Industries can power the world.
所以你最终是采用了稀土磁性材料吗
So you went with rare-earth magnetics in the end?
是的
Ah, yes.
在氰化物水晶矩阵里面
Inside a cyanide crystal matrix.
- 是蓝晶石 但是 - 蓝晶石
- It's kyanite, but… - Kyanite.
- 我可以试试吗 - 请
- Um, may I? - Please.
你有遵照安全行为准则的要求吗
You delivered on the safety protocols?
当然了 克里斯托只能联通电路
Oh, absolutely. Calisto only talks with electrical circuitry.
它的电流不会对人类 宠物 植物造成伤害
The current never touches people, pets, plants.
它是智能的 安全的
It's smart, and it's safe.
但是 要全面发售的话
Although, uh, in the spirit of full disclosure,
我得说它有一个小问题
I should mention one small thing.
针对女性客户 我们可以将它定制成各种颜色
It can be manufactured in pastel colors for the ladies.
你啊
You…
这就是我们想要的
Ah, well, this is it.
我们可以为所有人提供清洁能源
We can bring clean energy to everyone.
永不消竭
Sustainably.
克里斯托就是未来
Calisto is the future.
我终于将未来握于手中了
And I am holding the future in my hands, finally.
干得好 各位
Good work, guys.
干得好
Good work.
好了 我们来庆祝吧 吧台有酒
Come on, let's celebrate. Drinks in the bar!
（巴黎）
保持姿势 格挡
Keep your form. Block.
一 二
One, two.
帮我解开 绑紧一点
Let's take this one off. Make it tighter.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
巴黎还不错 对吧
Paris is not so bad, right?
你租了那个光线充足的公寓了吗
Did you take the apartment with the good light?
是的 但你要是送我植物的话
Yes. But if you get me a plant…
- 我会直接把它弄死的 - 当然了
- I'm just gonna kill it. - Of course.
没错
D'accord, d'accord.
我准备好接新任务了
I'm ready for a new assignment.
听着 我已经约了一个新客户见面了
Listen, I've set a meeting with a new client.
一个企业吹哨人
A corporate whistle-blower.
正要组一个团队
Putting a team together.
- 一个团队 - 是的
- A… A team? - Yes.
嘿 波士利
Hey, Bosley.
- 你要见我 是吗 - 是的
- You wanted to see me, right? - Ah, yes.
嘿
Oh, hey.
你是前军情六处忍者
You're the former MI6 ninja.
琼（六月）吗
Is it June?
是 简
Oh, Jane.
哦 简 简 不是六月哈
Oh, Jane. Jane. Not the month.
你是萨布里娜吗
Sabrina?
萨比娜 是个意大利名字
Sabina. It's Italian.
那你是意大利人吗
Oh, are you Italian?
不是 我 可能是吧
No. I… Maybe…
我们在汉堡有个新案子 是个新客户
We have a situation in Hamburg, a new client.
汉堡 有意思 汉堡不是汉堡的发明地
Hamburg. Interestingly, not where hamburgers were invented.
汉堡的发明地是法兰克福
That was in Frankfurt,
但法兰克福熏肠也不是法兰克福人发明的 这很
where frankfurters were not invented, which…
- 我不觉得这是 - 不好意思 我吃素的
- I don't think that this is… - I'm sorry. I'm vegetarian.
非常感谢你 但是我记得我听说过
Thank you very much. But I recall hearing.
你们俩在里约合作得很愉快
you two worked well together in Rio.
我记得她把我从屋顶上推下去
I recall her pushing me off a roof.
我记得那时刚好是撤退时间
I recall it was time to go.
呵 难怪啊
Heh. That makes sense.
客户是谁
Who's the client?
跟我来
Follow me.
（汉堡）
- 埃琳娜 - 嗨
- Elena? - Hi.
欢迎
Welcome.
是波士利先生吗
Uh, Mr. Bosley?
- 叫我波士利就好 - 谢谢你来见我
- Just Bosley. - Thank you for seeing me. Um…
- 您要点些什么吗 - 请给我浓缩咖啡
- Would you like anything? - Uh, espresso, bitte.
我不用了 谢谢
Merci, ?a va.
浓缩咖啡
Espresso.
COS附近情况确认
COS perimeter check.
COS
"Cos"?
我完全不知道那是什么意思
I have less than no idea what that means,
但是从这上面看 你是安全的
but you are good up here.
我想说
I would say,
附近无威胁
the coast is clear.
没错 就是这样
Yes, exactly.
这件事我考虑了很多
I have thought about this a lot.
我们要做的就是把它交给布洛克先生
All we have to do is get it to Mr. Brok.
我已经试着联系他了
And I have tried to contact him.
踏出这一步是非常艰难的
Well, it takes a lot to come forward,
我很佩服你的勇气
and I appreciate your courage.
你确定你要冒这个险吗
You sure you wanna take this risk?
是的
Yeah.
好的 我们可以帮助你
Okay, we can help you.
- 情况有点失控了 - 别叫了 你太可爱了
- It's just getting out of hand. - Stop it, you're so cute.
我要养条狗
I gotta get a dog.
这已经让我夜不成眠了
I can't sleep at night,
明明知情 却什么也不能说 什么也不能做
knowing and not being allowed to do or say anything about it.
我可以修好它
I can fix it,
我只是需要一个机会而已
but I just need the opportunity.
我相信你 你可以拿到证据吗
I believe you. Were you able to get the evidence?
这是我所有的报告和研究数据
All my reports, all my data.
您要点些什么吗
What can I bring you?
您的小票 先生
Your check, sir.
那是信号吗
Was that the signal?
- 埃琳娜 - 出什么事了
- Elena… - What's happening?
你得去趟洗手间
You need to go to the ladies' room.
- 不 我不用 谢谢 - 动作快
- No, I'm fine. Thank you. - Quickly.
嘿 出什么事了 简
Hey, what's happening? Jane?
就现在
Now!
喂 该死
Hello… Oh, shit!
该死
Shit!
该死 该死 该死
Ah! Shit, shit, shit!
那是我的枪
That's my gun.
萨比娜 快点
Sabina! Hurry!
- 开车 - 开车
- Go! - Go!
对 带客户走 我刚刚就想说这个
Yeah! Evac the client! That's what I was gonna say!
哇哦
Whoa!
怎么回事
What's going on?
- 天啊 你不是服务员吗 - 不是
- Oh, God. You're not a waitress? - No.
我是简 很高兴见到你
I'm Jane. Nice to meet you.
- 你带了大家伙了吗 - 在后面
- Did you bring the big gun? - In the back.
- 麻烦你挪下脚好吗 - 好 好的
- Can you move your feet? - Oh, sure. Mm-hm.
你知道怎么用吗
Oh, do you know how to use that?
该死的混蛋
Motherfucker!
我的天 他在朝我们开枪吗
Oh, my God! Is he shooting at us?!
- 抓紧了 女士们 - 啊
- Hold on, ladies. - Whoa!
啊
Whoa!
那是坦克吗 我的天 他去哪了 他去哪了
Is that a tank? Oh, my God. Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
- 我觉得我们甩掉他了 - 对付这女孩需要这么大手笔吗
- I think we lost him! - Bit much for just this girl, no?
这小妞是谁
Who is this chick?
我是谁
Who am I?!
你是谁 他又是谁
Who are you?! Who is he?
为什么他朝我们开枪
And why is he shooting at us?
车开稳一点
Keep it steady.
我的天啊 我死定了
Oh, my God. I'm gonna die.
不 他回来了
Oh, no! He's back!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
卧槽
Oh, shit!
该死的
Merde!
趴下 快趴下
Stay low. Stay low.
- 听我信号急转弯 - 准备好了
- Do a J-turn on my mark. - Ready.
就是现在
Now!
波士利
Bosley.
别动
Stay down!
简
Jane!
嘿 我说躺着别动
Hey, I said, stay down!
嘿 别动
Hey! Stop moving!
吃三明治吗
Sandwich?
三文鱼的
It's tuna.
也有可能是芝士的 不过不太好吃
Unless it's cheese, and it's not good.
你呢 你饿吗
How about you? You hungry?
查理向你们慰问 天使们
Charlie sends love, Angels.
她是谁 她是谁
Who is she? Who is she?
嘿 她被吓到了 而且全身都是呕吐物的味道
Hey, she's in shock, and she smells like puke.
你是谁
Who are you?
- 我是波士利 - 波士利
- I'm Bosley. - Bosley?
波士利是我们组织里的职称
Bosley's a rank in our organization.
就像是中尉一样
It's like a lieutenant.
你见的那个男人叫埃德加·德桑齐
The real name of the man you met was Edgar Dessange.
埃德加
Edgar.
简 节哀
Jane, I'm really sorry.
- 我知道他对你意义深重 - 噢 我不需要你的拥抱
- I know how much he meant to you. - Oh, I don't need a hug.
我需要
Well, I do.
他也是我的朋友
He was my friend too.
拥抱总是有用的
Hugs work.
好了 我们去休整一下吧
Okay, let's get you cleaned up.
走吧
Come on.
那辆车是偷来的吗
Is that a stolen car?
好吧
Okay.
波士利342 开启6号安全屋
Bosley, 342. Open Safe House 6.
波士 还有谁知道我们要在汉堡和埃琳娜见面
Boz, who else knew we were meeting with Elena in Hamburg?
按规定来说 没人知道
Well, protocol would be not to tell anyone.
你为什么这样问
Why do you ask?
因为 波士利
Well, Bosley…
埃德加认为
Edgar thought…
好吧 你没有亲眼见到这个家伙
Okay, you didn't see this guy.
他是职业杀手 为了这个一个小鱼小虾
He was a pro, and he brought quite a lot of firepower.
有必要带这么些火力威猛的武器吗
for such an easy target.
对啊 他戏超多的
Yeah, he was so extra, right?
要抓这个妹子 我一个苍蝇拍就够了
I could take that girl out with a flyswatter.
他竟然开了一辆超大型的武装机车
He rocks up in this urban assault vehicle.
所以我们猜测他是
So we're thinking what? He was…
也许她是被监视的对象
Maybe she was being watched…
但是如果是我们呢
but what if we are?
- 谁会监视我们 - 嘿 我洗好了
- And by who? - Hey, you guys. All cleaned up.
- 感觉好点了吗 - 嗯 谢谢
- Feeling better? - Yes, thank you.
我现在好像开始懂了
I'm kind of getting this, you know.
你们应该是女间谍
You guys are like lady spies and…
我只想知道这个人是谁
I just need you to explain who this guy is.
- 还有为什么他要追杀你们 - 噢 是你
- and why was he shooting at you. - Oh, you.
- 他是在追杀你 - 简
- He was shooting at you. - Jane.
追杀我
At me?
- 天啊 - 嘿
- Oh, God. - Hey.
- 好了 - 喝点茶吧
- Okay. - Just have some tea.
这个杀手就是个幽灵 面部识别系统近几年
The shooter's a ghost. Facial recognition's popped him.
在几个地方发现过他的踪迹 但是除此之外 没有名字 也没有任何记录
in a few places over the years but no name, no record, nothing.
说明他肯定是有背景的咯
He's got friends in high places then huh.
- 我要杀了他 - 我可得提醒你
- I'm gonna kill him. - I'm obliged to remind you,
查理最不喜欢复仇了 简
Charlie frowns on revenge, Jane.
好了 霍夫林小姐
So, Ms. Houghlin,
你的资料显示 你是卡利斯托项目的系统工程师
your file says you are a systems engineer on the Calisto project.
额 你竟然知道卡利斯托
Uh, you know about Calisto?
我们知道很多事情
We know about a lot of things.
我们知道你是麻省理工的优秀毕业生
That you graduated top of your class at MIT,
你周日会去学马伽术 你骑车去上班
you take Krav Maga on Sunday, you ride your bike to work.
你觉得你穿黄色好看
You think yellow is one of your colors.
但是我们都知道 黄色谁穿都难看
when, in fact, it's no one's.
我们还知道 如果你的约会网站头像
That you could be dating more.
能突出一下你的颧骨 你可能会有更多的约会机会
if you played up the cheekbones in your online profile pictures.
但是我们不知道的是 为什么有人要你死
What we don't know is why someone wants you dead.
我知道我能修好它的
I know it can be fixed.
我们一步步慢慢来
Let's take this one step at a time.
系统里有个漏洞
There's a flaw in the system.
这个漏洞是什么
What's the flaw?
卡利斯托可以被武器化
Calisto can be weaponized.
我是说 我能修好这个漏洞 但是现在
I mean, I can fix it. But right now,
任何感兴趣或是想犯罪的 有点能力的黑客
any decent hacker, curious or criminal enough,
都能把卡利斯托变成人体电磁脉冲装置
could turn Calisto into an EMP on the human body.
一种电磁脉冲
An electromagnetic pulse.
基本上就是脑梗
A brain seizure, essentially.
- 没错 - 看到没 我不是花瓶
- Yes. - See? I know stuff.
它会扰动神经系统
It disrupts the neural networks.
看起来就像是中风 或是动脉瘤
and looks like a stroke or an aneurysm.
所以使用者的踪迹是完全无法追查的
So it can be used without a trace of evidence.
一个完美的暗杀机器
A perfect assassination machine.
没错 利用我所创造的网络系统
Yeah. And it can be triggered remotely.
它还能远程狙击目标
across the network that I created.
很酷啊 看吧 如果上课好好听
Dope. See, that is what you can do.
- 你就能发明这种东西 - 还有谁知道这件事
- if you pay attention in school. - Who else knows about this?
当我发现我的同事差点死了的时候 我就在安全检查时
I filed a report after it almost killed my colleague.
上报了 但是我觉得它应该被掩盖了
during a security test, but I think it was buried.
我说的是我的报告 不是我的同事
My report, not my colleague. No.
胡里奥没事 他 额
Julio is fine. He, uh…
他只是再也没办法说话 也看不见颜色罢了
He just can't speak or see color anymore.
这东西还没量产吧
It's not in production yet is it?
没有 我们没有按计划完工 但是我们现在有六个原型
No, we're behind schedule, but there are six prototypes.
在布洛克仓库 还有一个在我的实验室
in the Brok facility vault, plus the one at my lab.
我想用那个来修好设备
that I was using to program to fix, which…
我们把那些原型机弄出来吧
Let's get those prototypes out of there.
额 不好意思 能暂停一下吗
Uh, I'm sorry. Can we just hit pause for a second, please?
你们公司有没有带有你们员工
Does your company have a website.
头像的网站呀
with an employee directory with photos?
有 但是布洛克工业的安全级别是地狱级的
Yes, but Brok Industries is equipped with insane security.
- 你们不可能 - 好了
- There's no way… - There we go.
你觉得她的卡还能进去吗
Do you think she still has security clearance?
如果进不去的话
If she doesn't, we'll know.
我们就能知道威胁来自公司内部 所以不管怎样
the threat comes from within, so either way…
- 我们都会拿到我们要的信息 - 不不不
- We get the information we need. - No, no, no.
不不
No, no.
- 噢 - 不
- Ooh! - No.
- 不不不 - 我
- No, no, no. - I…
嗯嗯
Huh. Hm…
- 锅盖头 - 锅盖头
- Bowl cuts. - Bowl cuts.
锅盖头
Bowl cuts.
就锅盖头了
（已授权）
等等 等等
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
拉夫 我只是想进去工作
Just trying to get to work, Ralph.
额 我也得做好我的工作啊
Well, I gotta do my job too.
好吧
Okay.
- 新发型哈 - 嗯
- New look, huh? - Mm-hm.
我很喜欢
I like it a lot.
拉夫 你这样会耽误别人的
Aren't you holding people up, Ralph?
额
Well…
祝你今天开心
you have yourself a good day.
别忘了要微笑噢
And don't… Don't forget to smile, yeah?
什么
What?
你们是怎么 你们怎么进来的
How… How did you even get in the…
天啊 你对普拉迪普做了什么
Oh, God. What did you do to Pradeep?
普拉迪普·普拉萨德
Pradeep Prasad.
没什么 普拉迪普没事
Nothing. Pradeep's fine.
我今天早上在健身房偷了他的证件
I nabbed his ID card from the gym this morning.
嗨
Hi.
再见
Bye.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
那斯万呢
And Sven?
我压住了他的颈动脉
I compressed his carotid.
让他的脑部缺氧
and deoxygenated his brain stem.
什么
What?
听起来很痛啊
Well, that sounds painful.
嗯 更像是打了个瞌睡
Yeah, it's like taking a nap.
闻见一股焦面包味 然后眼前一黑
You smell burnt toast, then everything goes dark.
别担心 他会醒的
Hey, don't worry, he's gonna wake up.
那可不一定
Heh, unless he doesn't.
- 什么 - 我们得走了
- What… - We should go.
如果他们下次巡逻 我们还在这栋楼里面的话
If we're in the building when they do their next security sweep,
我们全得进德国监狱
we're going to German prison.
那我们每天都得吃炸猪排了 每天噢
Hm, and then it's schnitzel. All the time.
听起来也不赖
Not such a bad deal, actually.
萨比娜 你从去保险库里找卡利斯托
Sabina, you get Calisto from the vault.
埃琳娜 你去拿你实验室里的原型机
Elena, you get the prototype from your lab.
我去引开守卫
I'll keep security distracted.
好了 准备好了吗
Okay. You ready?
额 击掌一下 妹子合心
Yeah. High five. Girl power.
噢
Oh.
谢谢
Thank you.
这次别吐
No puking.
（进入保险库 冷藏室）
一堆巴哥的破机器
Buggy piece of shit.
噢 不
Whoa… No.
- 波士 你在吗 - 在呢 怎么了
- Boz, you with us? - I'm here. What do you got?
卡利斯托不见了 不在这里
Calisto's gone. It's not here.
有人先偷走了
Someone beat us to it.
事情更有趣了哈 你知道是谁吗
The plot thickens. Can you get an ID?
（主菜单 进入保险库记录）
查到了 一个叫皮特·弗莱明的人
There we go. Some guy. Peter Fleming.
我们等等看埃琳娜那边有什么收获
Let's see what Elena comes back with.
等等 我们可能有另一个麻烦了
Hold up. We might have another problem.
那个普拉迪普出现了
Your boy Pradeep just showed up.
普拉迪普没去做单车操吗
Pradeep didn't spin?
但是他都买好优惠劵了啊
But he signed up for the Groupon and everything.
他在楼下了
Well, he's here.
- 拉夫 - 怎么了
- Ralph? - Yeah?
普拉迪普·普拉萨德在前台
We've got Pradeep Prasad here.
但是系统里显示他已经进了大楼了
The system says he's in the building.
嗯 系统出了点小问题
Yeah, there's a glitch.
我觉得是这部电脑以为埃琳娜·霍夫林是
I think the computer thinks Elena Houghlin is…
我现在埃琳娜·霍夫林的照片发给你
Right now, I'm sending you an image of Elena Houghlin.
你发给所有人 抓住她
Get it to all our guys. I want her.
- 拘留审问 - 收到
- detained for questioning. - Yes.
她在实验室里
She's in her lab.
走吧
Let's go.
警卫队来了
And here comes the cavalry.
他们在集中人手 姑娘们
The heat is assembling, ladies.
噢 他们知道了
Oh, they know.
好了 我们撤离点见
All right, meet me at the pickup.
萨比娜 我这边很难搞
Sabina? This one's real hard.
我需要你引开别人的注意力
I need you to exhibit some attention-seeking behavior.
正合我意
I have so many ideas.
霍夫林
Houghlin?
她在哪儿
Where is she?
- 她在哪 - 我不知道
- Where is she? - I don't know.
- 等等 等等 - 什么
- Wait, wait, wait. - What?
- 我找到她了 - 哪儿
- Now I got her. - Where?
在这里
Here.
十一层
Eleven?
各位 她在十一楼 十一楼 女洗手间
Guys, she's on 11. Level 11, women's restroom.
嗨 额 你是谁
Hi. Uh, who are you?
嘘 坐好 把手放在我能看到的地方
Shh. Sit down. Keep hands where I can see them.
你是安全检疫部门的吗
Are you with Health and Safety?
天哪 这东西真难开
God, these things are impossible to open.
额 你好像不该乱碰这里的东西吧
Um, you're really not supposed to be touching things in here.
除非你是上面派来检查的
unless you're supposed to be touching things in here.
你用嘴撕开的
You put your mouth on it.
人类嘴里有两千多亿细菌
Twenty billion bacteria reside in the human mouth.
你真可爱
You're adorable.
简 简 你在调情吗
Jane? Jane, is that you flirting?
嘿
Hey!
站住 嘿
Stop! Hey!
说你呢
Hey!
噢 搞笑吧
Oh, come on.
准备好了吗
You ready?
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
- 对不起 - 嘿
- Sorry! - Hey!
噢 天啊
Oh, my God!
回来
Get back here!
谁看见她了
Who has eyes on her?
她在四楼放了把火
She set a fire on four.
我们跟着她到了三楼
We are following her to three.
- 我们快追 快 - 三楼吗 她在十一楼
- Let's go, guys! Come on. - Three? She was on 11.
哦哦哦哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
你怎么
What did you…
- 拿好这个 - 好的
- Hold this. - Okay.
噢 那不是 那不是你啊
Oh, that's… That's not you.
不是
No.
- 拿好 - 好
- Hold this. - Okay.
能帮我拉一下拉链吗
Can you unzip me?
额 好 好
Yeah, yeah. Uh…
不好意思
Sorry.
再见
Bye.
- 你不要了吗 - 送你了
- You don't want your… - Keep it!
- 喂 - 嘿 苏珊
- Hello? - Hey, Susan.
弗莱明先生想让你马上到实验室来
Mr. Fleming would like you in the lab right away.
- 我马上就来 - 好的 谢谢
- I'll be right there. - Okay. Thanks.
- 你看到她了吗 - 嗯
- Did you see her? - Yes.
别看屏幕上的 用双眼看
Not on-screen. With your eyes!
- 你们去那边 你们去那边 快 - 是
- You go there, you go there. Now! - Okay!
我出来了
I'm out.
- 在大堂 我看到她了 - 哪里
- Main lobby. I see her! - Where?!
大堂 在大堂
Lobby level. Lobby level!
快点 快追
Let's go, guys. Come on!
把手放在我能看到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
趴在地上 快
Get on the ground! Now!
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
- 快点 - 怎么了
- Do it! - What for?
我不知道 我不知道 啊
I don't know. I don't know! Ah!
我到底怎么了 你们在找什么 啊
I don't know what for. What are you looking for? Ah!
抱歉了 苏珊
Sorry, Susan.
苏珊·奥森
"Susan Olsen."
封锁所有出口 从下往上一层层排查
Put all the exits on lockdown. Sweep from the bottom up.
简 我拿到了
Jane. I got it.
其他原型机不见了 我们得快走 有人抢先拿走了
The unit's gone. We need to go. Someone beat us to it.
你在开玩笑吧 它们被偷了吗
Are you kidding? They were stolen?
- 噢 不不不不 - 噢
- Oh, no, no, no! - Oh!
- 噢 - 天啊
- Oh! - God!
有什么办法吗 有没有其他出口
Any ideas? Is there another way out?
等等 我应该能黑掉这个系统
Wait, wait. I can hack this.
把这个改造成电磁脉冲 然后让整个电路超载
Turn it into an EMP, overload the electronics in the door.
会对我们造成伤害吗
Won't that kill us in the process?
如果靠得太近就会 我想如果远一点应该没问题
It's short proximity. We should be okay if we keep our distance.
- 多远 - 额
- How far? - Uh…
我猜这里应该够远了吧
Here is far enough, I guess.
你猜的 科学家都靠猜吗
You guess? Do scientists usually guess?
当然 那是科学方法的第一步
Of course. It's the first step in the scientific method.
假设
Hypothesis.
卡列斯托 短程电力爆破
Calisto, short-range power burst.
好了 正在蓄电 正在蓄电
Okay, it's powering up. It's powering up.
应该能行
This should work.
- 是拉夫 - 别去
- Ralph. - No.
天啊
God.
- 我还有时间 - 不
- I have time. - No.
- 我得救他 - 不 别过去
- I have to. I have to. - No. No. Stay here!
拉夫 拉夫 快过来
Ralph? Ralph. Get over here now.
- 你在这啊 - 拉夫 那里快爆炸了
- There you are. - Ralph, it's about to blow.
我没办法把它停下来 快过来
I can't stop it. Get over here.
你觉得我会听你的吗
You think I'm gonna listen to you?
- 拉夫 快过来
- Ralph, come! Get over here now!
- 把手放在我能看到的地方
- Put hands where I can see them!
我们走吧 那东西还有用吗
Let's get out of here. Do we need that?
- 已经没用了 - 那就别管它了
- No, it's useless now. - Then leave it.
再不走就走不了了 姐妹们 快走 我们得走了
Move it or lose it, ladies. Let's go. We gotta go.
快 快上车
Come on, come on. Get in.
你觉得拉夫会没事吗
Do you think Ralph's gonna be okay?
噢 当然 他肯定吉人天相的
Oh, yeah. I'm sure he's fine.
- 他看起来没什么大碍 对吧 - 嗯
- He seemed fine, right? - Yeah.
我想 他一定 他一定没事的
I'm sure… I'm sure he's okay. I'm sure he's fine.
额 真可惜啊
Oh, well, that's a shame.
很显然 这次的挫折确实让人失望
Obviously, this is a disappointing setback,
但是我们还有时间
but we have time.
这样吧 你让约翰接电话
Do you know what? Just get John on the phone.
马上
Now.
那就叫醒他
Well, then wake him up.
你没事吧
Everything all right?
电话能借我吗
Can I have your phone?
（柏林）
波士利 342
Bosley, 342.
欢迎来到汤森事务所的柏林分部
Welcome to the Berlin outpost of the Townsend Agency.
有东西吃吗 我快饿死了
Is there food? I'm starving.
女人永远吃不饱
All women are starving all the time.
- 亲爱的 - 大家好 欢迎回家
- Mi chico. - Here they are. Welcome back.
亲爱的 你好吗
Mi amor, como estas?
- 很好 - 那就好
- Very bien. - Good.
- 那就好 - 额
- Cool. - Well…
嘿
Hey.
你欠我一次波比跳了啊
You owe me a burpee now, okay?
- 嘿 孟买妹妹 你还好吗 - 大师好
- Hey. Bombay sister. How are you? - Master.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
- 这是埃琳娜 - 很高兴见到你
- This is Elena. - Pleasure to meet you.
- 这是圣人 - 哇
- Saint. - Wow.
哇 你身上有种耀眼的能量
Wow. You have this beautiful energy.
- 谢谢 - 嗯
- Thank you. - Yeah.
- 天老爷啊 - 噢 怎么了
- Oh, Jesus. - Oh, wait, what?
- 天啊 天啊 - 怎么了
- Oh, my God. Yeah, um… - Oh, no.
我想帮你调整一下背部的骨位
I would love to apply a firm touch to your back.
- 你同意吗 - 额 当然
- Do you consent? - Yeah, sure.
好吧 我试试看
Okay. Just let me try to find this.
- 噢 噢 - 噢
- Oh! Oh. - Oh, yeah.
- 噢 - 好了吗
- Oh. - Good?
嗯 很舒服
Oh, yeah, yeah. Amazing.
肋骨错位 很常见的
Displaced rib. Very common.
如果你还需要其他调整 我随时为你服务
If you ever need additional adjustments, I'm here for you.
圣人专门照顾我们的健康和饮食
The Saint takes care of our health and well-being.
- 让我们随时有精力战斗 - 额 我尽力而为
- Keeps us in fighting shape - Yeah. Well, I try.
他滋养我们的大脑 身体 和灵魂
He feeds our mind, body and soul.
噢 我们应该花点时间悼念一下埃德加吧
Oh, should we take a moment to remember Edgar?
我准备了晚餐
I prepared a mini feast.
来纪念我们美好的朋友
to honor our beautiful friend.
我有黑色羊乳干酪 帕尔玛奶酪 曼彻格芝士
I got Pecorino Nero, Parmigiano-Reggiano, Manchego,
- 还有 最重要的 - 谢了
- and, of course… - Thanks.
- 他最喜欢布里干酪了 - 嗯
- He loved Brie. - Yeah.
- 啊 还有红酒 - 特别是红酒
- Ah! And wine. - Especially wine.
哇 我还以为你们会吃什么
Wow, I thought you guys were gonna serve,
豆芽 或是小麦草之类的
like, bean sprouts and wheatgrass.
所谓饮食就是你在食物中
Eating is all about the intention.
倾注的意念
you put into your meal.
如果你尊重那头牛
If you honor the cow,
那它产出来的奶酪 一定对你的身体好
the cheese is gonna be good for you.
对了 我知道现在这个情况
By the way, I understand the circumstances.
你肯定很有压力
that brought you here have been stressful.
- 超级有压力 - 如果你需要聊天
- So stressful. - If you ever need to talk,
我还是个执业心理治疗师
I'm a licensed psychotherapist.
哇 我总算知道你们为什么叫他
Wow. I can really see why you guys call him…
- 圣人了 - 好了
- The Saint. - Yes. Okay.
- 噢 我这里还有电解质水 - 好呀
- Oh, electrolyte-enhanced water? - Mm, fine.
噢 还有 吃一片这个 对你的口气有帮助
Oh, and also try this. It's really good for your breath.
- 噢 谢了 - 没事
- Oh, thank you. - Good.
我把最后一个进保险库里的人的证件号
I sent the ID of the last person to access the vault.
录入系统里了 调取了汉堡所有的监控
through our search system, ran every CCTV.
和安保摄像头
and security cam in Hamburg.
弗莱明 那是我 那是那个掩盖我报告的人
Fleming. That's my… That's the guy that buried my report.
- 嗯 - 看 这里
- Hm. - Look. There.
他五分钟前在机场里
He was at the airport five hours ago.
- 所以他离开了德国 - 带着箱子
- So he's left Germany. - With the case.
他知道卡利斯托有什么威力
He knows exactly what Calisto can do.
他知道在黑市里这东西能卖多少钱
He knows what it's worth on the black market.
如果他在卖这个东西 他肯定想要灭了你
If he's selling it, he'd want you out of the way.
- 我在扩展调查范围 - 不好意思打断一下
- I'm broadening the search. - I'm sorry.
是弗莱明想杀我
Fleming tried to have me killed?
可能 也有可能是买家的指示
Maybe. Maybe at the direction of a buyer.
坏人不喜欢事情出纰漏 这个新玩意是你设计的
Bad guys don't like loose ends, you made a fancy new toy…
但是 我是他的下属啊
But I worked for him. I mean…
他还跟我调过情呢
he flirted with me.
亲爱的宝宝
Oh, honey.
一个男人可以边爱你 边要你死
A man can love you and want you dead.
哈 我可不是这种人
Ha, not me.
我婚礼上还发生枪战了呢
There was a gunfight at my wedding.
- 等等 你结婚了 - 没有 我抢手着呢
- Wait, you're married? - No. I was the better shot.
好了 我想吃奶酪
All right. I need cheese.
奶酪 那是什么东西的代号吗
"Cheese." Is that a code for something?
额 它代指的是 我已经四十岁了 还单身
Yes. It's code for "I'm 40 and single,
我内心有个奶酪那么大的空缺急需填补
and I have a cheese-size hole in my soul to fill.
我为你内心的空缺准备了素食冰淇淋
I also have vegan ice cream for your soul.
我真懂我
You really know what I need.
我应该绕过弗莱明 越级上报的
I should have just gone around Fleming.
而不是循规蹈矩 遵守层及规则
and not followed some stupid chain of command.
我应该直接去找布洛克 我还是太傻太天真啊
Gone directly to Brok. But, no, I just rolled over.
你们应该不知道
You're probably the last people.
那是什么感觉吧
that would know what that feels like.
我从小到大都有被抛弃情结
I grew up with major abandonment issues.
因此做了不少缺心眼的事情
It led to some pretty self-sabotaging behavior,
害得我被送到了好几家少管所里
which landed me in various institutional facilities.
查理把我保了出来
Charlie bailed me out.
如果不是查理的话
And if it wasn't for Charlie…
我可能就已经死了 或是回到监狱里 所以 我懂你的
I'd probably be dead or back in prison, so I feel you.
我基本上是在无助和悔恨的边缘长大的
I pretty much grew up on the corner of powerless and ashamed.
等等 你不是住在派克大街吗 你是富二代吧
Wait. You grew up on Park Avenue. Aren't you an heiress?
富人有富人的烦恼
More money, more problems.
你呢 查理怎么找到你的
So, what about you? How did Charlie find you?
简以前是军情六处最年轻的特工
Jane is former MI6. Youngest recruit ever.
你为英国情报组织效力吗
You worked for British intelligence?
是曾经
She said "Former."
我也曾循规蹈矩
I also followed the rules.
层级规则也不适合我
The chain of command didn't work out so well for me either.
拉夫死了
Ralph's dead.
我杀了拉夫
I killed Ralph.
我 我是个杀人凶手
I'm… I'm a murderer.
- 不 - 不不不
- No. - No, no, no.
附带伤害而已
Collateral damage.
我不会把这笔账记在你身上
I wouldn't take that on.
现在问题是 如果卡利斯托落到坏人手上的话
The point is, if Calisto falls in the wrong hands…
我是说 我们得在它伤害更多人之前把它抢回来
I mean, we have to get it back before it hurts more people.
机会来了
Well, now's our chance.
弗莱明先生刚刚在伊斯坦布尔入境
Mr. Fleming just cleared passport control in Istanbul.
- 噢 不 - 不
- Oh, no. - No.
你跟伊斯坦布尔有什么过节
What's your problem with Istanbul?
我吃了隔夜的没有煮熟的羊肉和酸奶汁
I got food poisoning from undercooked lamb.
食物中毒了 然后我又饿了
and yogurt sauce I left out, but then I got hungry.
- 你呢 - 肯定是和你不一样的原因
- What about you? - Not that.
我们失陪一会儿
Will you excuse us?
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
为了保证那个杀手离我们远点
I wanna be sure that assassin stays away from us.
这次行动要保密 直到我们查出所有的幕后玩家
We should keep this quiet until we know who all the players are.
我们不知道这个卡利斯托是什么 或是谁想要
We don't know what this Calisto is or who wants it,
所以我们要谨慎行事
so let's play it safe.
那位拉尔夫杀手怎么办
What about Ralph-killer in there?
带她去衣帽间 配上装备
Take her to the closet, gear her up.
如果有人问起 就说我们去巴西
And if anybody asks, we're going to Brazil.
好的
Okay.
伊斯坦布尔
Istanbul.
埃琳娜·霍夫林怎么处理
What about Elena Houghlin?
你知道该怎么做
I think you know what to do.
（伦敦）
我拆开看了
I took it apart.
什么都没有 没有跟踪器
Nothing. No tracker.
没有发出任何信号
It's not emitting any signals.
你担心什么
What had you worried?
老实说 我不知道
To be honest, I don't know.
就是感觉
A feeling.
骨子里的
Something in the bones. Hmph.
老习惯了
Old habits.
也许只是你太想念这份工作了
Perhaps it's simply that you miss the job.
我们都会变老的 我的朋友
We all get old, my friend.
退休并不是判了死刑
Retirement is not a death sentence.
不想退休的人还好意思说我
Says the man who refuses to retire.
抱一下
Mm, come on.
怎么了
What?
确实有东西在你的骨头里
Something in the bones, indeed.
谁会这么对你
Who would do this to you?
一个知道我对她起疑的人
Someone who knows I'm on to her.
谢了
Thank you.
我的天啊
Look at this.
这简直是我梦寐以求的衣帽间
This is the closet of my dreams.
我真的可以随便拿吗
And I just get to take whatever I want?
- 是借 - 哦
- Borrow. - Oh.
真有这个规矩么
Is that an actual rule?
好了 所以你要从基础保护层开始
Okay. So you wanna start with a protective base layer.
我推荐这件珠绣内衣 怎么样
I recommend a beaded camisole. Yeah?
哦 某种高分子材料制成
Oh. Some kind of polymer material.
额 防弹的 复合防弹衣
Uh, bulletproof, composite body armor.
它最初是作为航天器的保护层的
It was originally developed as a protective layer for spacecraft.
没错 这款内衣可不扎胸 科技进步带给女性的福音
Yeah. And it's a bra that doesn't dig. Progress.
准备得怎么样了
How we doing down here?
啊 还在第一层啊
Ah, we're still in the first closet.
还有一个衣帽间吗
There's another closet?
嗯 打开军械库
Hm. Armory open.
简 我想给你看个东西
Jane, I wanna show you something.
- 哇哦 - 来 看看这个
- Whoa. - Come on, check it out.
- 过来 戴这个试试 - 哦 谢谢
- Here, try these on. - Oh, thank you.
为什么 这有什么功能 哇哦
Why? What do they do? Whoa!
这眼镜功能绝了 哇哦
What do they do? Whoa.
额 你比我想象得要年轻
Huh. You're younger than I thought.
我过去生活艰辛
I've lived hard.
你可以把你麻省理工的学位
Think you can put that MIT degree to use.
- 用在这样的东西上 - 这是什么
- with something like this? - What is it?
通用接口 可以让你侵入几乎所有设备
Universal Interface. Lets you hack into almost anything.
嗯 把几乎去掉 是所有设备
Mm-mm, not almost anything. Everything.
- 这里有一个新产品 - 是什么
- So here's the new baby. - What's that?
高速来复 用来发射麻醉剂
High-velocity rifle, customized to fire tranquilizer darts.
非致命 反应迅速 非常之高效
nonlethal, fast-acting, very potent.
简 你有新玩具了
Jane, you have a new cuddle buddy.
哦 上帝啊
Oh, Jesus.
我们给埃琳娜安装通讯设备吧
Shall we fit Elena with comms?
我觉得可以
I think so.
嗷 就是那种入耳式的吗
Oh, that in-ear radio thing you guys have?
比那更好
Ah, even better.
它是一种皮下发射器
It's a subdermal transmitter.
通过骨骼传导 看
Works through bone conduction. See?
所以我要去纹身吗
So I'm getting a tattoo?
额 不是 纹身是天使通过努力才能获得
Uh, no. Tattoos are earned by Angels over time.
会给你一个临时版本的
You'll get a less permanent version.
是的 通讯器隐藏在手镯里
Yeah, comms are concealed in the link.
只要你戴上它 就可以听到我们
As long as you have it on, you can hear us.
酷 嘿 我可以拿一盒薄荷糖么
Cool. Hey, can I take these mints?
不行 别碰这些薄荷糖
No. Avoid the mints.
还是不要到处乱摸了
Actually, let's just stop the touching around here.
- 你知道的 有些东西会爆炸 - 哦
- You know, some of this blows up. - Oh.
（伊斯坦布尔）
这个地方简直太棒了
This place is amazing.
它是世界的十字路口 危险和金钱的代表
It's the crossroads of the world. Danger and money.
我们要找出弗莱明和他的买家交易的地点
We need to figure out where Mr. Fleming's meeting his buyer.
取回卡利斯托
and get Calisto back before it becomes.
在它成为每一个坏蛋最爱的新武器之前
every bad guy's favorite new weapon.
- 像行李箱核武器 - 宠物老虎
- Like suitcase nukes. - Pet tigers.
- 喷气式滑雪板 - 水上摩托艇
- Jet Skis. - Sea-Doos.
极速跑车
Cars that go fast really furiously.
所以我们要怎么找到他
So how do we find him?
我们现在已经脱离了事务所 所以
Well, we're off the agency's grid here, so…
我们该怎么找到他 我们走上街头 用老办法
How do we find him? We hit the streets. We go old-school.
用钱 用拳头换消息
We sling some bills. We get violent.
我感觉自己今天像只老虎 或者豹子
I feel like a tiger today, maybe a leopard.
但不管怎样 我都要狂野起来
But either way, I am down to get wild.
这里我可能有联系人
I might have a contact here.
是我在军情六处时的线人
An asset from when I was with MI6.
额 可能是指
Uh, "Might" As in?
她一定住在这儿
As in she definitely lives here,
但她恨死我了
and she definitely hates me.
练习练习你的英语
Practice your English?
- 早上好 - 早上好 很好
- Good morning. - Good morning. Well done.
- 糖果 - 糖果
- Candy! - Candy.
你依然对当地的孩子这么好啊
Still spoiling the local kids?
你 离我远点
You. Get away from me.
法蒂玛 等一下 求你了 跟我聊聊
Fatima, wait. Please, just talk to me.
找别人聊去吧 我不能再跟你有任何瓜葛
Talk to someone else. I can't get involved with you again.
法蒂玛 拜托等一下
Fatima, please wait.
我已经等过你了
I waited for you already.
还记得么
Remember?
对不起我失信了 但我已经不再为军情六处工作了
And I wasn't there for you, but I don't work for MI6 anymore.
- 我现在为这些人工作 - 我不在乎
- I work for these people now. - I don't care.
我不会帮你的
I don't help you.
你知道原因
You know why.
他们资金雄厚 非政府 是非政府组织
They are very well-funded. Non-governmental, NGO.
他们可以提供让你事业运转起来的一切
They can get whatever you need to get up and running today.
没有无尽的等待 也不会违背承诺
No waiting. No broken promises.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我只跟你喝杯茶
It's only tea.
你想让我做什么
What do you want from me?
你见过这个男人吗
Have you seen this man?
或许
Maybe…
你知道谁见过
you know someone who has.
拜托了 我可以帮你
Please. I can help you.
重建诊所
Rebuild the clinic.
- 你现在倒是能帮我了 - 对不起
- You can help me now? - I'm sorry.
当他们告诉我 我的线人很安全时 我相信了他们
I believed them when they told me my asset was safe.
我相信了你 但我却失去了所有
And I believed you, but I lost everything.
我不得不拒绝那些我再也帮不上忙的未婚妈妈
I had to turn away unwed mothers I could no longer help.
我知道
I know.
所以我选择退出
It's why I quit.
让我们重建对彼此的信任
But let me rebuild our trust.
我给你带了一些日常用品
I brought you the usual.
就在外面
It's right outside.
带我去看看
Show me.
我可以在六个月内再给你一批货
I can get you another shipment in six months.
四个月
Four.
那需要多久你能找到我们想要的人
So how long will it take for your sources to find our guy?
我们真的需要
Because we really need to…
这就是医生订的吗
Is this what the doctor ordered?
好吧 我们开始卸货吧
Okay. Let's get this off the street.
好的
All right.
干得漂亮 简
Good job, Jane.
你要找的人在一个酒店 帕夏酒店
Your man is in a hotel. The Pasha Hotel.
易卜拉欣·帕夏吗
The Ibrahim Pasha?
你知道谁能把我们带到他的房间么
Do you know anybody who can get us into his room?
当然
Of course.
这个卡车我也要了
I will take the van too.
没问题
Of course.
他在帕夏 我们出发
Pasha. Let's go.
我们尽可能多地了解一下弗莱明的伊斯坦布尔之行
Let's learn all we can about Mr. Fleming's trip to Istanbul.
弗莱明出去的时候 我们进去
When Fleming goes out, we go in.
复制他的设备 收集他所有通讯信息
Double his devices. Gather all his communications.
交易时间 地点 和谁
The when, the where, the who.
他一直在看哥斯达黎加的房子
He's been looking at property in Costa Rica.
他有一个海外银行账户
And he's got an offshore bank account.
搞定
Gotcha.
我呢 我该做什么
What about me? What should I do?
你应该已经死了 所以你就放松一下吧
Seeing as you're supposed to be dead, why don't you relax.
弗莱明会认出你的 我们不能冒险
Fleming could recognize you, and we can't risk it.
不了 谢谢 我吃饱了
No, thank you. Full.
混进去
Let's get in there.
简 他快到了
Jane, he's almost there.
萨比娜 现在给他发短信
Sabina, text him now.
先生 你还好么
Sir, is everything all right?
我找不到帽子了
No, I can't find my hat.
我帮你找帽子
Let me help you with that.
- 你的帽子 - 谢谢 谢谢
- Your hat. - Thank you. Yes. Thank you.
你看见我的手机了吗
Have you seen my phone?
- 你的包 - 哦 谢谢
- Your bag. - Oh, thanks.
- 哦 它在这 - 谢谢
- Oh, there it is. - Thank you.
好了 都在这了 我们调查了他的通讯记录
Alrighty, here it is. We filtered his communications,
看来弗雷明明天要在土耳其德比马赛上
and it seems Mr. Fleming is selling Calisto.
把卡利斯托卖掉
tomorrow at the Turkish derby.
于华里马场
Veliefendi Hippodrome.
当然 这个特别的赛马场
Of course, this particular racetrack.
很受富商的欢迎
is popular with a syndicate of wealthy businessmen.
毫无疑问这里和
No doubt with connections.
国际军火交易 毒品贩卖 还有
to international arms deals, drug trade and…
所有有可能对卡利斯托感兴趣的人有关
All parties who might be interested in Calisto.
熟记你的身份 辛迪加成员
Familiarize yourselves: syndicate members,
受邀参加的马匹富商
wealthy horse owners expected to attend.
标注弗雷明可能交易的人
Flag anyone Fleming could be in business with.
我想帮忙
I wanna help.
听着 我不只是一个吓坏了
Look, I am not just some frightened girl.
需要你们保护的姑娘
in your witness protection program.
如果你们需要帮忙进出某个地方 我可以做到
If you need help getting in and out of someplace, I can do it.
我可以侵入任何系统 而且操作很快
I can hack any system, and I can do it fast.
你们需要我 波士利女士
You need me, Mrs. Bosley.
不要说我不行因为我知道我可以
And don't tell me I can't do it because I know I can.
我 我受够了一直闲着 我
I am… I'm done sitting still. I'm…
我体验过一次 我想要更多
I've had a taste. I want more.
我想加入
I want in.
我曾经看到一个很胖的孩子
You know, I once saw a really fat baby.
和一只猫碰鼻子
giving Eskimo kisses to a kitten.
他比你可爱多了
And that was more adorable.
这个例子也是在暗示既然让你参加会议
Also, it's implied that you're coming.
就表示你已经加入我们了
because you're in this briefing.
她给了你黑客设备
Yeah, she gave you the universal hacking tool.
和手镯 不是吗
and the bracelet, right?
嗯 是的
Mm-hm. Yeah.
那是什么感觉 看起来好像还不错的样子
But how'd that feel? It looked like it felt really good.
- 非常不错 - 我是打算等我看完
- Felt nice. - I was just gonna give you.
- 就把平板给你的 - 嗯
- the tablet once I was done. - Mm.
- 额 可以继续了 - 好
- Uh, carry on. - Great.
我想说的是
As I was about to say,
有很多地方要覆盖到
there's a lot of ground to cover,
所以我们要分开行动
so we're gonna need to spread out.
埃琳娜 你就是我们的天眼
Elena, you'll be our eye in the sky.
监控主机就在记者席里
The track's mainframe's located just inside the press box.
我们会把你送进去 你黑进监控系统
We'll get you in. You hack into the security cameras.
监视弗莱明
Watch for Mr. Fleming.
简负责人群控制
Jane's on crowd control.
土耳其德比马赛吸引了成千上万的观众
Turkish derby attracts thousands of spectators.
我们要进行扫描和评估
who need to be scanned and assessed.
站得高 望得远
Start low, go high.
从你的位置
From your nest,
你可以提供战术支持
you can provide tactical support.
清除一切阻碍行动的威胁
Take out any threats to the operation.
萨比娜 你负责地面比赛
Sabina, you'll run the ground game.
一旦目标出现 你负责抓捕
Once the target's on site, you make the grab.
我们要一举擒获弗莱明 买家和卡利斯托
We need Fleming, his buyer and Calisto.
不许失败
No loose ends.
我来负责运输
I'll take care of the transportation.
并准备撤离计划
and prep for extraction.
我们要把所有人都带走
We're taking everybody out of there with us.
我刚好有辆车满足这个要求
I have just the vehicle to do it.
好乐 我进去了
Okay, and I'm in.
嘿 简
Hey, Jane.
啊 你在那儿呢
Ah, there you are.
通讯检查 萨比娜
Comm check. Sabina.
收到
Good.
- 简 - 收到
- Jane. - Good.
- 埃琳娜 - 收到
- Elena. - Good.
不要对着手镯说话
Don't talk into your bracelet.
我刚刚错过了一个连赢位置投注
I just missed a superfecta.
希望第三轮有好运
Better luck in the third run, I hope.
嘿 你买的哪个
Hey, what's your bet?
额
Um…
蓝色的
The blue one.
喔
Mm.
离预约时间还有六分钟 有发现吗
Six minutes to post time. Anybody see anything?
没有
Nothing yet.
简 你有什么发现吗
Jane, you got anything yet?
没有
Nothing.
抱歉 他是谁
Excuse me, who is that?
阿利姆·哈桑
Alim Hassan.
卡塔尔王子
Qatari prince.
- 哦 卡塔尔王子 - 是的 相当有钱
- Oh, "Qatari prince." - Yeah, serious money.
- 相当有钱 - 拥有上百匹马
- "Serious money." - Owns hundreds of horses.
- 拥有上百匹马 - 是的
- "Owns hundreds of horses"? - Yeah.
我们知道了 他很有钱
We get it. He's rich.
他是买家吗
Is he the buyer?
我这里看不到
I don't have an angle.
萨比娜 是弗莱明
Sabina! Fleming.
是他 穿浅蓝色西装
That's him. Light blue suit!
没错 他来了
Yeah, he's here.
那绝对是他 萨比娜
That's definitely him. Sabina?
看到了
Got him.
货在他手里
He has the goods.
我准备行动
Moving in.
简
Jane?
在我的视线范围内 波士
In my sights. Boz?
车辆就绪
The ride is ready.
他在跟人讲话 灰色西装
He's talking to somebody. Gray suit.
那是买家吗
Is that the buyer?
- 是那个杀手 - 终于出现了
- It's the assassin. - Bae showed up.
如果你想在我之前杀了他
If you think you're killing him before I kill him.
我就先杀了你
I'll kill you first.
开枪 简 拿下他
Take the shot, Jane. Bag him.
- 该死 - 他们上车了
- Oh, shit. - They're in the Mercedes.
- 交易不在这儿进行 - 我们得走了 下来
- There's no sale here. - We gotta go! Get down here.
我来了
I'm coming!
该死
Shit, shit!
Shit!
在车上放个追踪器
Get a tracker on that Mercedes!
这就去
On it!
走 驾
Come on! Hyah!
快点
Come on.
我来了
Coming in!
快点 走开 走开 走开
Come on. Move, move, move.
- 快点 埃琳娜 - 我来了
- Come on, Elena! - I'm coming!
快 快 走
Go, go, go!
快点
Come on!
- 得儿驾 - 萨比娜
- Giddyup. - Sabina!
- 嘿 姐妹们 - 进来
- Hey, guys. - Get in here.
好了 踩油门吧
Okay, punch it.
- 我们出发 干得漂亮 - 嚯
- Here we go! Great job! - Whoo!
你怎么 我不知道你竟然会骑马
How did you… I didn't know you could jump horses.
- 钱越多 马越多 - 好吧
- More money, more horses. - Huh.
谁来追踪一下这辆车
Can somebody please track this mofo?
我们不能开这辆车追踪他们
We cannot tail him in this.
坐好了
Hold on.
他们正往北去准备出城
They're headed north out of town.
我们已经离开了市界
We've left city limits.
那儿除了采石场什么都没有
There's nothing out here but a rock quarry.
把数据调出来
Bring up the specs.
我在附近守着等你信号
I'll circle until you signal.
交易一定在这里进行
The sale will definitely go down here.
我们把东西都带上 不知道都谁在里面
Let's take everything. We don't know who's in there.
我 我觉得自己穿得过于隆重了
I-I think I'm a little overdressed.
好吧
Okay, um…
你需要这个
You need this.
我知道怎么可以进去了
I see a way in.
简 简 简
Ja… Jane! Jane!
走吧
Come on.
哈
Huh?
做梦吧你
In your dreams.
嗨
Hi.
他一会儿就醒了 快走
Hey, he's gonna wake up. Come on.
你把所有装备都拿走了
You've got all the dots.
我给你信号的时候你已经行动了
I signaled you, you went rogue.
- 我们要把他扔了吗 - 是的 来吧
- Should we toss him? - Yeah, let's do it.
兄弟 不管弗莱明在和谁做交易
Man. Whoever Fleming's in business with,
他都是活腻了
he is in way over his head.
把那扇门封锁 把他们困住
Seal that gate. Lock them in.
- 把这里的门锁好 - 好的
- Then lock yourself in here. - Okay.
这些是给你准备的
These are for you.
这可不是薄荷糖
They are not mints.
- 明白了吗 - 不是薄荷糖
- You got it? - Not mints.
- 走了 - 锁好门 记住不是薄荷糖
- Let's go. - Lock this. Not mints.
- 不是 我知道 - 锁门
- No, I know. - Lock it!
好的 门已经锁好了 还有一个出口有三层楼高
Okay, the gate is locked. Only other exit is up three stories.
干得漂亮 埃琳娜
Nicely done, Elena.
你来了
There he is.
- 弗莱明先生 - 是的
- Mr. Fleming. - Yes.
那是澳大利亚乔尼
That's Australian Jonny.
我们不是把他交给美国了吗
Didn't we hand him over to the Americans?
但他在这出现了
Well, he's here.
如果你想在我杀了他之前
If you think you're gonna kill me.
杀了我
before I kill him…
你刚刚是怎么说的来着
What was the thing you said?
所以 你是
So, uh, you are…
我代表一位不愿透露姓名的买家
I represent a buyer who wishes to remain anonymous.
啊
Ah.
- 让我们验下货 - 当然
- Let's have a look. - Of course.
伙计们 这就是卡利斯托
Guys, that's Calisto.
就是这个了
There we go.
钱呢
The money?
货到付款
COD.
还有电汇
Plus wire transfer.
很好
Great.
在我们结束交易之前
But before we close the deal,
我的老板想要一个小示范
my employer would like a little demonstration.
以确保这个设备具备你说的功能
just to make sure the devices do what you say.
你让我杀人
You want me to kill somebody?
劲爆哦
Damn.
不是我 是我的老板坚持
No, I don't, but my employer insists.
所以 随便选一个
So, yes. Pick anybody.
- 不能选我 - 额
- Obviously, don't pick me. - Uh…
- 西达姆 抓个人过来 - 额 不 不 不
- Sidam, go get somebody. - Uh, no, no, no.
额 我 我 我把报告给你
Uh, I-I-I gave you the report.
所有的功能都在里面 杀人不包括在交易里
It's all outlined in there, so that was never part of the deal.
这个嘛 弗莱明先生 现在包括了
Well, Mr. Fleming, it is now.
听着 这是一个复杂的过程 很明显 我不
Look, it's a complicated process. Obviously, I don't…
你甚至不知道它是怎么运行的 对吧
You don't even know how it works, do you?
它需要根访问
It'll require root access.
或一个世界级的黑客
or a world-class hacker.
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa, whoa!
你在想什么 该死
What are you thinking? Bloody hell!
这不是计划的一部分 霍达克先生（动画非凡公主希瑞中的人物）
That was not part of the plan, Mr. Hodak!
该死
Damn it!
波士 弗莱明死了
Boz, Fleming is down.
杀手是乔尼·斯密斯的人
The assassin works for Jonny Smith.
波士
Boz.
我们要行动了 准备好撤退路线了吗
We need to engage. Ready for exfil?
我们走 把东西拿好 赶紧离开这儿
Let's get out of here! Someone grab that. Get me out of here.
波士 他们要走了
Boz, they are leaving.
行不行动
Go, no-go?
她去哪儿了
Where the hell is she?
我没看到她
I can't see her anywhere.
门打不开
It won't open.
那就想办法
Well, then fix it.
上楼修好它
Go upstairs and fix it.
哦 不 姐妹们 有人来了
Oh, no. Guys, someone's coming.
他朝你们过去了
He's headed your way.
一起
Together.
- 在上面 - 糟了
- Up there! - Shit.
- 找到她们 - 哦 天呐 伙计们
- Find them! - Oh, my God. Guys?
- 快走 - 发生什么了
- Go! - What's happening?
我来对付杀手 掩护我
I'll take the assassin. Cover me.
快 快 快 快
Go. Go, go, go!
啊 是独立小姐啊
Oh, Miss Independent.
额 等我一分钟
Um… Uh, just a minute!
屋里有人
Um, ocupado.
喔 哦
Whoa! Oh…
- 你是谁 - 哈 疼
- Who are you? - Gah! Oh!
滚一边去 我会马伽术
Stay away. I know Krav Maga.
你在哪学的 商场么
Where you learn? Shopping mall?
一 二 三
One! Two! Three!
马伽术冲鸭 哈
Krav Maga! Yeah.
别开枪
Don't shoot.
澳大利亚乔尼 遇见我是你的荣幸
Jonny Australia, the pleasure is all yours.
来啊
Come on.
简 那个一键睡眠的按钮在哪
Jane, where's that sleepy-neck button?
我现在有点忙 自己搞定
I'm a little busy. Figure it out!
哦
Ooh!
埃琳娜 支援我
啊
Ah!
谢啦 埃琳娜
Thanks, Elena.
自从认识你那天起
I have dreamed of this moment.
我一直在幻象这个时刻 不过在我的想象中你是长头发
since the day I met you. Except your hair was longer.
但是这个发型我也喜欢 这个也挺好的
But I like this too. This is great.
- 想都别想 - 你想和我一起逃走吗
- Hey. Don't even think about it. - You want to run away with me?
你也太饥渴了
Oh, you're so desperate.
不准动 埃琳娜
Hey, stop right… Elena!
我想活着再见到你
I want to live to see you again!
关门啊
Close the gate!
太慢了
Too late!
简 你在哪儿
Jane, where are you?!
杀手正在逃跑
The assassin's getting away!
萨比娜
Sabina!
额
Uh…
埃琳娜 让这个东西停下来
Elena, stop this thing!
不行
No!
把箱子给我
Give me the case!
喔
Oh!
埃琳娜
Elena?
- 坚持一下 - 埃琳娜
- Hold on! - Elena!
埃琳娜
Elena!
天啊 哦 不
Oh, God. Oh, no!
快点啊 埃琳娜 我需要你 我需要你
Come on. Elena? I need you, man! I need you!
萨比娜 靠边站
Sabina, stay to the side!
太棒了
Awesome!
让我出去
Get me out of here!
放手
Stop it!
埃琳娜
Elena!
我快被碾进去了
It's about to get very crush-y in here!
简 我们需要你
Jane, we need you!
我就快拿到了
I've nearly got it!
简 快点
Jane, hurry!
简
Jane!
我来了
I'm on my way.
萨比娜
Sabina,
抓住
reach up.
简 简
Jane! Jane!
这个 这个 在那里
This one! This one! There!
感谢老天
Oh, thank God.
老天
Oh, God.
你还好吧萨比娜
You all right, Sabina?!
没事儿 迟来总比不来好
Yeah. Better late than never.
哈
Ha!
啊 贴反了
Oh, it's the wrong side.
新队员刚把自己弄晕了吗
Hey, did the rookie just tranq herself?
是的
Yup.
你男朋友去哪了
Where's your boyfriend?
- 霍达克 那个杀手 - 跑了
- Hodak. The assassin? - Gone.
把卡利斯托带走了
Took Calisto with him.
- 乔尼呢 - 他也跑了
- Where's Jonny? - He scurried off.
他是个小贱人
He's a little bitch.
波士去哪儿了
Where's Boz?
我们还是不要被抓到
We probably shouldn't be caught.
站在尸体旁边吧
standing over a dead body.
嗯 还穿成这样 不行
Not dressed like this, no.
她死了吗
Is she dead?
你想摸摸她吗
You want to touch her?
过来
Come on.
碰碰她
Touch her.
她是活的
She feels alive!
你把她吵醒了
You woke her up.
你好啊
Hey, you.
我们在船上吗
Are we on a boat?
是啊
Yeah.
- 波士利 - 波士
- Bosley! - Boz?
波士利女士
Ms. Bosley?
波士
Boz.
波士利们经常翘班吗
Do Bosleys usually leave?
不 这感觉不对
No, this is all wrong.
- 所以她是走了吗 - 我们被耍了
- So she's gone? - Well, we were made,
也许她是想去调查内鬼
so maybe she wanted to do a sweep.
也许吧
Maybe.
或者她
Or she's…
什么 不 她是第一个
What? No. Boz was the first Angel.
被提拔为波士利的天使 她和我们一样
to be promoted to Bosley. She's one of us.
她不是第一个叛变的天使
She would not be the first Angel to turn.
这种事发生过 你知道过去的事情
It's happened. You know the history.
是她提议从实验室把卡利斯托偷出来的
It was her idea to steal Calisto from the lab.
没错 但是弗莱明抢先一步
Exactly. But Fleming beat her to it.
我们的任务一直是把东西抢回来
It's been our mission the entire time to get this thing back,
但是它总是从我们手边上溜走 好像
and it just keeps slipping us, like…
我们不可能频繁失手 是 是她
We're better than that. It's… It's her.
弗莱明死了 卡利斯托没了
Fleming's dead. Calisto's gone.
她也消失了
And so is she.
乔尼说他是代替别人来交易
Jonny said he represented somebody…
如果这个人就是波士利呢
What if it's Boz?
是我房间的电话
That's my room.
喂
Hello?
查理托我向你问好 你们现在很危险
Charlie sends love. You're in grave danger.
- 快点出去 - 姐妹们
- Get out of there now! - Guys?
简
Jane?
埃琳娜 趴下 趴下
Elena, stay down! Stay down!
我是波士利
I'm Bosley.
让我带你离开这里
Let's get you out of here.
快
Quickly.
萨比娜
Sabina?
Sabina.
萨比娜
嗨 萨比娜
Hey. Sabina.
她对你很重要
She means a lot to you.
她是我的新朋友
We're new friends.
也许吧
I think.
这一周过得太难了
It's been a really tough week.
我不能再失去她
I can't lose her too.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
天呐
Oh! Oh, God.
- 啊 - 啊 天呐 对不起
- Ow! - Oh, God, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你哭什么
Why are you crying?
我没哭
Oh, I'm not crying. Heh.
你明明在哭 这是
Well, you are. That's…
这是
That's what's…
好啦 没错 我在哭
Okay, fine, yeah, I'm crying.
我没想到你
But I didn't think that you…
会在乎我
cared about me.
为什么这么想
Why?
因为
Because…
因为你认为我没有任何感情
Because you don't think I have any feelings.
不是 我
No, I…
我很烦人
I can be really annoying.
不过是大多时候
Most of the time.
你是特别烦人
You can be so annoying.
我不是故意的 只是
I don't try to be. It just sort of…
我不像别人那样会善于隐藏真情实感
I don't have the filter thing people have.
- 你好 - 我不知道
- Hey. - I don't know.
这是什么做的 但是它救了你一命
what this is made of, but it saved your life.
谢谢你
Thanks.
埃琳娜在哪
Where's Elena?
不知道
I don't know.
我们得找到她 所以我打了电话找人帮忙
We have to find her, so I called in for some help.
- 因为我被炸飞了 - 没错
- Because I got blown up? - Yeah.
也是因为
But also because…
你说服了我 不需要每件事都靠自己
you convinced me I don't have to do everything by myself.
做得好
Well done.
天使们你们好 你们差我一个解释
Hello, Angels. You owe me an explanation.
这里不是巴西
This is not Brazil.
- 嗨 - 我带了补给
- Hey. - I brought supplies.
自己做的添加了益生菌的康普茶
Homemade kombucha with probiotics.
最重要的是
And the best part…
我带了个朋友
I brought a friend.
是你 你这个叛
You. You trai…
- 嘿 - 简
- Hey! - Jane.
我不是内鬼
I'm not the mole.
那你为什么在这里
Then why are you here?
和你一样
The same reason you are.
我本来应该死了
I should be dead.
你打给我之后她就打给我了
She called me right after you did.
我有草药敷布可以治淤青
I have an herbal compress for the bruises.
- 没人想要 - 好吧 那你肿着吧
- Nobody wants that. - Okay. Keep your bruises.
那究竟是谁
So then who?
- 就当在自己家一样 - 谢谢
- Make yourself at home. - Thank you.
我让人送了点衣服来
I had some clothes sent up.
随便挑
Take your pick.
这么正式干嘛
Um, why so formal?
不好意思 这是另一个总部吗
I'm sorry, is this another headquarters?
你有简和萨比娜的消息吗 她们会来吗
Have you heard from Jane and Sabina? Will they come?
这么好奇
So inquisitive.
像猫一样好奇
Curiosity of a cat.
或者说像雪貂一样
Or a ferret.
真是个科学家啊
It's the scientist in you, isn't it?
只是想知道我现在的处境
Just trying to understand my situation.
你想有一位观众听你和布洛克先生讨论卡利斯托
You wanted an audience with Mr. Brok to discuss Calisto.
马上就有了
Well, soon you'll have one.
但是卡利斯托已经被偷走了 所以我
But Calisto's been stolen now, so I…
干得好
Well done.
我很满意 计划成功了
Satisfying when a plan comes together.
给你们一点隐私
We'll give you some privacy.
天呐
Oh, my…
- 不可能 - 是真的
- No way. - Oh, yes.
我跟踪了他几个星期
I've been tracking him for weeks.
他降落在伊斯坦布尔的时候
When he landed in Istanbul,
我知道我得在他抓住你们之前
I knew I needed to get to him.
抓住他
before he got to you.
波士他们要走了 行不行动
Boz, they are leaving. Go, no-go?
波士
Boz.
该死
Damn it!
抱歉我离开了采石场 但是
I'm sorry I left the quarry, but…
更抱歉的是 我来得太迟了
more sorry I was too late.
我确实不敢相信 一个波士利会背叛我们
I just can't believe that. A Bosley?
你刚才很快就得出结论是我干的
Mm, you had no trouble believing it was me.
- 你听到啦 - 嗯
- You heard that? - Mm.
那个澳大利亚乔尼
Australian Jonny.
- 那个逃走的家伙 - 嗯 又逃掉了
- The one that got away. - Yeah, again.
上次我看到他
The last time we saw him,
- 我们在里约 然后 - 你把我推下了楼
- we were in Rio, and then… - You pushed me off a roof.
- 你得忘了这事 - 天呐
- You have got to get over that. - Oh, my God.
我正在这么做 只是在慢慢消化
I am. Just processing.
所以最后见到他的人是
So then the last person to see him was…
- 是波士利 - 没错
- Was Bosley. - Exactly.
乔尼没有去监狱
When Jonny didn't make it to jail,
所以查理怀疑波士利叛变了
Charlie suspected Bosley had gone rogue.
结果发现他在建立自己的圈子
It turns out he's building his own network,
把服务卖给出价最高的人
selling his services to the highest bidders.
他现在在利用我们跟罪犯做生意吗
He's using us to date criminals now?
嗯 乔尼 霍达克 就是那个杀手 他们都为他效力
Yeah. Jonny, Mr. Hodak, that assassin, they work for Bosley.
他一直看起来像个怪胎
He always seemed like kind of a weirdo.
很古怪 很英国人
Freaky. English.
- 所以波士利抓了埃琳娜 - 嗯
- So Bosley has Elena. - Mm-hm.
- 我们知道地点吗 - 当然
- Do we know where? - Of course we know.
大部分衣服里都有追踪器
There's trackers in most of the clothes.
你公寓里有很多皮夹克
You have a lot of leather jackets at your apartment.
- 看到没 我跟你说了是借的 不能拿 - 嘘
- See, I told you it was borrow and not take. - Shh shh…
布洛克正在他家的豪宅开派对 埃琳娜在他那儿
Brok is hosting a party at his compound. Elena's there.
（夏蒙尼 法国）
每年他都要召集富人和美女
Every year, he brings together the wealthy and beautiful.
参加他的年度“幻想派对”
for his annual Vision Party.
今年他正打算向投资者展示卡利斯托
This year, he's planning to present Calisto to investors.
为什么波士利要带埃琳娜去布洛克那儿
Why would Bosley want to take Elena to Brok?
我猜是把鸟人带回阿尔卡特拉斯岛上（俗称恶魔岛，曾是军事监狱）
Bringing the Birdman back to Alcatraz, I guess.
谁
The who?
是部电影 伯特·兰卡斯特演的
It's a movie. Burt Lancaster.
鸟人 迈克尔·基顿
Birdman. Michael Keaton.
- 不对 迈克尔·基顿是蝙蝠侠 - 不对 本·阿弗莱克是蝙蝠侠
- No, Michael Keaton is Batman. - No, Ben Affleck is Batman.
他像吗
I mean, is he?
我是这里唯一认识伯特·兰卡斯特的人吗
Am I the only person here who knows who Burt Lancaster is?
- 我得了脑震荡 - 好吧
- I'm concussed. - Doesn't matter.
- 这是部老片子 是… - 你多大岁数了
- It's an old movie. It's from… - How old are you?
我多大 什么 这个无关紧要
How old am I? What? That has nothing to do with it.
- 我没看过你的推荐信 - 有各种年龄段的
- I don't have your references. - There are film buffs…
- 电影爱好者 - 我们还是去接我们的女孩吧
- of all ages. - Let's go get our girl.
你想对我做什么
What do you want with me?
你翻了你妈妈的衣橱才找到这个吗
Did you raid your mom's closet for this?
她还跟你玩过别的吗
What else of hers do you play with?
我一生的工作都在评估女性的才能
I've spent an entire career estimating the talents of women.
而你 亲爱的
And you, my dear,
你聪明得令人赞叹
are marvelously clever.
你背叛了她们
You betrayed them.
你背叛了天使
You betrayed the Angels.
我不再为汤森德事务所工作了
Well, I no longer work for the Townsend Agency.
我退休了
I was retired.
你来给我演示
So you are going to show me.
怎么破解这个东西 重新编辑根访问
how to hack this and reprogram root access…
把权限给我
to me.
你以为弗莱明可以做到
You thought Fleming could do it.
他总是有一个习惯
He always had a habit of claiming credit.
抢不属于他的功劳
he didn't deserve.
- 需要多久 - 做梦 我不会碰它的
- How long will it take? - Forever. I'm not touching it.
哈哈 你以为你有选择
Ha, ha, you think you have a choice.
真可爱
It's adorable.
她们会 她们会来问候你的
They'll send… They'll send love.
她们会问候你们的
They'll send love.
挺顽强啊 看来你一直在学习
Ooh, feisty. You've been studying.
我希望她们来
I hope they come.
这栋别墅有四层 大约60个房间
The compound has nearly 60 rooms on four levels.
有36名保安负责这个派对
There's 36 security guards contracted for the party,
还有布洛克的私人保镖
plus Brok's private crew.
这是我喜欢的歌
That's my song!
你也想喝吗
Oh, did you want one?
- 没事 - 好吧 我们开始吧
- I'm good. - Okay, let's do this.
埃琳娜被困在顶层 西北角
Elena's being held on the top floor, northwest corner.
救她是首要任务
She's our priority.
- 嗨 - 这层楼不对外开放
- Oop! Hey. - This is a private floor.
我就转了个身 这个地方太大了
I'm just turned around. This place is huge.
我在找洗手间
I was looking for the bathroom.
我真的想要去嘘嘘
It's just that I really need to pee.
我走错了吗 我想也许
Am I in the wrong place? I thought may…
好梦
Sweet dreams.
我们进来了
We're in.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
悄悄地 用不暴露自己的方式消灭敌人
To neutralize an enemy discreetly and anonymously.
这是我工作中的黄金原则
That's a gold standard in my business.
你认为这是缺点 我却认为是天赋
What you deem a flaw, I deem a gift.
这个天赋不仅提供权力
One that not only provides power…
而且授予权力
but confers it as well.
你们在我的办公室干什么
Whoa, what are you doing in my office?
布洛克先生 天呐 感谢老天 请帮帮我
Mr. Brok? Oh, my God. Thank God. Please help me.
- 她在这干什么 - 这些人
- What is she doing here? - These men…
约翰 我有点不懂 我以为你都搞定她了
John, I'm a little confused. I thought you handled her.
搞定我
Handled me?
居然是你
It was you?
你想阻挠我
You wanted to sabotage me.
你在期待什么 花吗
What were you expecting, flowers?
还是手写的感谢信
A handwritten thank-you note?
把她除掉
Get rid of her already.
其实我觉得她对我们还是有用的
Actually, I believe that she can still prove useful.
- 你知道他是谁吗 - 知道啊 我的全球安全主管
- Do you even know who he is? - Yes. My global security chief.
约翰刚刚从皮特·弗莱明那里拿回了卡利斯托
John's just recovered Calisto from Peter Fleming,
那个目光短浅又贪婪的叛徒
that shortsighted, greedy traitor.
他们杀了他 他们杀了弗莱明
They killed him. They killed Fleming.
我不听 我不听
Whoa, whoa, la-la-la-la-la!
这是你的问题 好吗
This is the problem with you, right?
一直跟我说我不能知道的事情
You keep telling me shit I can't know.
合理的借口 你听说过吗
Plausible deniability. You ever heard of it?
你真是个糟糕的员工
You're a terrible employee.
哼 谁在乎有人死了 对吧
Yeah, and who cares if people die, right?
只要投资人开心
As long as the investors are happy.
成熟一点 小姑娘
Grow up, little girl.
卡利斯托将改变世界
Calisto is about to change the world.
如果你想烤蛋糕 你就得打破几个鸡蛋
If you want to bake a cake, you got to break a few eggs.
是煎蛋卷 如果你想把死人比作鸡蛋
It's omelet. If you're gonna compare dead people to eggs,
能不能起码把词用对
could you at least use the correct phrase?
我不该在这里 你是安全隐患
I shouldn't be here, ha, ha. You're a security threat.
你负责处理她 你起的头 你来收尾
You take care of her and finish what you started.
计划就是这样
That's exactly the plan.
借过 我还要开派对呢
Oh, excuse me. I have a party to host.
- 让一让 - 请坐 布洛克先生
- Yo, Tats, move. - Take a seat, Mr. Brok.
搞什么
Uh, no.
现在是怎么回事
Sorry, what the hell's happening here?
天呐
Oh, my God.
放我出去
Let me out now.
我是你的老板
Sorry, you work for me.
好吧 我是你们所有人的老板
All right, all of you work for me!
你个笨蛋 哈哈
You dumbass. Ha, ha.
你笑什么
Why are you laughing?
你个笨蛋
You idiot.
他们把卡利斯托从你这偷走了
They're stealing Calisto from you.
他们要把它当作武器 暗杀别人
They're gonna use it as a weapon. To assassinate people.
滴滴滴
Beep, bop, bloop.
滴滴哒 滴滴滴
Bloop, beep, bloop, boop, boop!
- 应该行了 - 我也这么觉得
- That ought to do it. - I think so.
请你授予根权限 布洛克先生
If you would grant root access, please, Mr. Brok.
你疯了
Heh, you're crazy. Heh, heh.
我不会给你权限的
I'm not giving you my access.
你会改变区块链
You could alter the blockchain.
你会毁了它 你真的会毁了一切的
You could ruin it. You could literally ruin everything.
啊 嗷
Ow! Ow!
我们的计划是推出卡利斯托
Our intention is for Calisto to be released.
让它上市 就跟计划好的一样
into the market as planned.
实际上 让我黑进去的单元越多
In fact, the more units there are out there.
越好
for me to hack into, the better.
别给他 他们把所有知道这件事的人
Don't do it. They've killed everyone.
都杀了 只剩下你和我了
who knows about this except you and me.
布洛克先生是两起杀人案的同谋
Mr. Brok is complicit in the deaths of two people.
- 喔 - 现在我很乐意把这事告诉
- Oh… - Now, I am very happy.
我在执法部门的老同事
to inform my former colleagues in law enforcement.
你好 亚历山大
Hello, Alexander.
已获得根权限
Root access granted.
∮ 我所做的就是赢 赢 赢 ∮
∮ All I do is win, win, win. ∮
∮ 不管怎样我脑子里想着钱 ∮
∮ No matter what Got money on my mind. ∮
∮ 我永远无法摆脱它 ∮
∮ I can never get it off. ∮
你不接吗
Do you want to answer that?
不接
No.
∮ 我所做的就是赢 赢 赢 不管怎样 ∮
∮ All I do is win, win, win No matter what. ∮
好吧
Yes.
∮ 在我的脑海里，我永远无法摆脱 ∮
∮ …on my mind I can never get it off. ∮
这下好了 这是在警告有人试图打开
Oh, great. It's an attempted access alert.
我的私人保险柜
on my personal safe.
亲爱的 轮到你了
You're up, my dear.
去死吧
Go to hell.
让我看看我能不能让你改变心意
Well, let me see if I can change your mind.
也许我再给你一个愉快的惊喜 你就会听话
Perhaps if I gave you another delightful surprise.
兰斯顿 天呐
Langston. Oh, my God.
他一直被锁在这里
He's been in there all the time.
你把人藏在我路易十四的柜子里
You hid a person in my Louis XIV?
你有毛病吗
What is wrong with you?
没有幽默感 这是你的问题
No sense of humor, that's your problem.
我刚才在想是你就好了
I was hoping it would be you.
- 贱人 - 友情提醒
- Bitch. - Fair warning.
上次见面之后 我交了个朋友
Since we last met, I made a friend.
简 情况怎么样了
Jane, what's the update?
我们快搞定他了
Yeah! We're almost done with him.
你在这儿等着
You sit tight.
转换根权限
Switching root access.
名字和大拇指指纹
Name and thumbprint.
约翰·波士利
John Bosley.
你好约翰 根权限已授权
Hello, John. Root access granted.
- 好了 - 好姑娘
- Done. - Good girl.
当然 我得确认下它是不是真的好用
I'll have to check, of course, that it's actually working.
卡利斯托 启动短程能量爆发
Calisto, short-range power burst.
- 命令不能改写 - 啊 等等
- No override. - Ah, whoa, whoa!
你在做什么啊 会害死我们的
What are you doing? It will kill us.
别傻了 只会杀了她
Don't be daft. It will kill her.
以及那个不知道名字的家伙 我们不会死
And what's-his-name. Not us.
我们下楼享受你的派对 走吧
We're gonna be downstairs enjoying your party. Come on.
你想让我下楼 假装一切都好吗
You want me to go down there and pretend everything's fine?
一切都好啊
Everything is fine.
你将要颠覆能源行业
You're gonna disrupt the power industry!
你会是最棒的
Go, you.
退休比我想的要好
You know, retirement is better than I expected.
我很抱歉 兰斯顿 天啊
I'm so sorry, Langston. Oh, God!
啊
Ah!
那个家伙是个十足的混蛋
That guy is a total dick.
- 你拿到了吗 - 当然了 姐妹 有我罩你
- Did you get it? - Yeah, girl, I got you.
当然拿到了
Of course I got it.
你们好好玩儿
Have fun, guys.
回见
See ya!
- 借过 抱歉 - 嘿
- Excuse me. Sorry! - Hey.
这是你的派对 亚历克斯 享受吧
This is your party, Alex. Enjoy it.
这个世界不太平 亚历克斯
The world is on fire, Alex.
但我肯定你这一代人会找到办法的
But I'm sure your generation is gonna figure it out.
- 有人吗 救救我们 - 这里肯定有钥匙
- Hey, help us! - There must be a key somewhere.
我的导师埃德加
You see, it was my mentor, Edgar,
教会了我在搏击中怎么获胜
who taught me how to win a fight.
你以为你之前战胜了我两次吗 不
You thought you beat me twice before? No.
我是在学习
I was learning.
霍达克先生 你有七种招数
You've got seven moves, Mr. Hodak.
我全都知道了
I know them all.
七招
Seven moves…
和脆弱的自尊心
and a fragile ego.
怎么会这样
Why is this happening?!
- 找到她了 - 干得好
- Got her. - Good job.
- 太好了 - 萨比娜 天呐
- Yes! Oh, ho, ho! - Sabina! Oh, my God.
- 你来找我了 - 这一身太好看了
You came for me. Look at you.
- 那个东西怎么闪个不停 - 那个啊 没什么问题
- Why is that thing doing that? - Oh, that? That's nothing.
我刚编辑了程序 就是让它闪一闪 响一响
I just programmed it to light up and make noises.
你们俩跟我走
You two, with me.
请一直走到出口 找人帮帮他
Directly to the exit, please. Get this man help.
冷静一下 出去 所有人都出去
Calm down. Get out. Everybody go.
出去
Just get out.
你真的以为你能杀了我 老东西
Do you really think you'd kill me, old badger?
瑞贝卡 我真是这么想的
You know, Rebecca, I really did.
我的名字是波士利
My name is Bosley,
我要揍扁你
and I'm gonna kick your ass.
你以为我在工作了40年之后会安静地离开吗
You expect me to go quietly after 40 years?
这是我的职业
This is what I do.
你寡不敌众 天使
You're outmanned, Angel.
你总是这样
You always have been.
杀了她
Kill her.
天使向你问好
Send the love.
英格丽德
Ingrid?
看来你一直挺忙的啊
You've been busy.
你怎么会
How did you…
在商言商 约翰
It's just business, John.
他现在和我合作了
He's with me now.
我明白了
I see.
我建立了这家事务所 让它逐渐发展壮大
You know, I built this agency from the ground up.
查理死了 公司应该是我的
It was supposed to be mine after Charlie died.
但我被挤出去了
I was pushed out.
你指望我会做什么 从事园艺吗
What did you expect me to do? Take up gardening?
你以为是你造就了我们 是我们造就了你
You thought you made us. We made you.
- 没错 我们一直信任你 你个混蛋 - 晚
- Yeah, we trusted you, you dick. - Good nigh…
我话还没说完
I was in the middle of my speech.
抱歉啦
Sorry.
算了
All right, well…
清理干净 天使们 干得好
Sweep it clean, Angels. Good job.
你想去加州训练成为一名天使吗
So you want to go to California and train to be an Angel?
什么 我
What? I…
真的吗 你们
Really? You…
- 天呐 - 我们在招募你
- Oh, my God. - We are recruiting you.
成为一名天使 就像
To be an Angel like…
- 像你和简一样 - 我们走
- you and Jane? - Let's go.
不然你以为我们一直在做什么
What do you think we've been doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以为你挺聪明的
I thought you were smart.
这不是你的优点吗
Isn't that your thing?
完成了 查理
It's done, Charlie.
我决定了怎么处理埃琳娜·霍夫林
And I decided what to do with Elena Houghlin.
- 怎么做 - 她现在是我们的新队员了
- What's that? - She's our new recruit.
很好 谢谢你 波士
Good. Thank you, Boz.
谢谢你告诉我
I appreciate the call.
- 你们在加利福尼亚都训练什么 - 跳过飞机没
- What do you do in California? - Ever jumped out of a plane?
- 我不太做高空运动 - 哦 呃
- I don't really do heights. - Oh, um…
- 和鲨鱼一起游过泳吗 - 嗨 是你
- Have you swam with sharks? - Hey! It's you.
你能憋气多久
How long can you hold your breath?
和鲨鱼一起吗 不太长
Sharks? Not long.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Oh, hey. - Hi.
你怎么啦
What happened to you?
等等 你俩认识
Wait, you guys know each other?
- 嗯 我当时在吃三明治 - 是
- Yeah, I was eating a sandwich. - Yeah.
- 我走进去 然后你给了我 - 磷
- I came in, and you gave me the… - The phosphorus.
磷是我最喜欢的化学物质
That's my favorite chemical.
- 因为你当时 - 没错 混合了
- Because you were… - Exactly, mixed with…
呃 是你们
Um, did you…
是你们干的吗
Did you do that?
是的
Oh, uh, yeah.
他终于“戳”到点子上了
I think he, uh, finally got the point.
这是双关吗 因为你刺穿了他
Is that a pun? Because you impaled him?
你是在说笑话给这个帅呆子听吗
Are you doing, like, a joke thing for the handsome nerd?
- 我没有 - 挺好笑的
- Of course not. - I mean, it's working,
如果你是在说笑话的话
if that is what you're doing.
如果我想联系你
So if I'm trying to get in touch with you,
- 我怎么做才好 - 别担心 我会找到你的
- how would I do that? - Oh, don't worry. I'll find you.
是你干的
You did that?
嗯
Yeah.
埃琳娜·霍夫林
Elena Houghlin.
凯丽·加勒特
Kelly Garrett.
欢迎来到汤森德事务所
Welcome to the Townsend Agency.
拐最后一个弯的时候你松油门了
You lifted coming into the last corner.
你得相信车子 再来
You got to trust it. Go again.
手举起来 不要怕
Hands up. No fear.
与疼痛作斗争
Fight through the pain.
注意力集中
Focus.
这次试着坚持90秒
Try to last 90 seconds this time.
你们必须按照正确的顺序
You must clip the wires.
剪断电线 不然你就会
in the correct order, or you will…
- 好了 - 爆炸
- Done! - …blow up.
很好 你没有死 霍夫林
Good job not dying, Houghlin.
其余人 清理干净 重新来
The rest of you, clean up and start again.
霍夫林 起来 我们走 离跳伞还有10秒
Houghlin, get up! Let's go! Ten seconds to jump!
- 所有人都起来 - 好的
- Everybody up! - Okay.
我一点都不怕 我们冲啊
I'm not freaking terrified at all! Let's go!
老天在上 今天请多多关照
Heaven above, watch over us today.
别让我成为真的天使
Don't make me a literal angel.
我一辈子都在为这个时刻做训练
I've been training for this moment my whole life!
好了 各位新成员 终极挑战
All right, recruits! One final challenge!
露丝·巴德·金斯堡（美国联邦最高法院大法官）99年跳下去的时候
When Ruth Bader Ginsburg made this jump in '99…
她也是天使吗
RBG is an Angel?
你什么都没听到
Forget I said that!
跳吧
Let's make it happen!
成为天使吧
Be the love!
跳吧 克洛伊 跳
Go, Chloe, go! Let's go!
跳吧
Get out of there! Let's go!
你去哪儿
Where do you think you're going?
你需要降落这架飞机 霍夫林
You need to land this bird, Houghlin.
我希望在地面上见到你
I hope I see you on the ground.
祝你好运
I really, really do.
稍后见
Later.
该死
Shit!
该死 好了好了
Shit. Okay, okay.
天呐
Oh, my God.
好的
Okay.
- 我想死她了 - 太好的
- Oh, I've missed her! - Yes, yes!
这就对了 宝贝 降落下来
That's it, baby! Bring her down!
- 好样的 好样的 - 耶
- Yes, yes, yes! - Yeah!
- 喔吼 - 好样的
- Woo-hoo! - Yes!
喔
Whoo!
- 真的是她啊 - 太棒了
- There she is! - Yes!
做得好 你做到了
Good job. You did it!
感谢你们能来
Thank you for coming.
- 你做到了 - 我降落了
- Of course you did. - I landed.
我们一点都不担心
Dude, we weren't worried.
- 有点吧 - 我知道
- A little worried. - I know.
让我闻闻你的嘴
Let me smell your breath.
- 她竟然没吐 - 噢
- She didn't even puke! - Oh!
天呐
Oh, my gosh.
耶
Yeah!
在椅子上签名 正式一点 什么都别想
Okay! Sign the chair, make it official. Don't think about it.
来来来 来一小杯 干了 干了 干了
Here we go, here we go. Shots, shots, shots!
你熬过了训练
You made it through training.
我很紧张
Okay, I'm so nervous, you guys.
- 天呐 - 来
- Oh, my God! - Here.
- 啊 酒 我需要酒 - 它能减轻疼痛
- Oh, shots. I need it. - That'll help.
好了
Okay.
来吧
Voilà.
准备好了吗 坐好了 女士
You ready? Ass in the chair, lady.
- 开始吧 - 好了 好了
- Let's go. - Okay, okay.
天呐 我想纹在这里
Oh, God. Guys, I think I want mine there.
是个好地方吗 我觉得这里不会太疼
Is that a good place? I don't think that hurts as much.
- 很好 - 如果疼痛等级是从1到10
- That's very sweet. - Okay, on a scale of one to 10,
这个到底有多疼 说实话
how much does it hurt? Be honest.
- 告诉我 - 我已经感觉不出疼了
- Just tell me. - I no longer feel pain.
比中弹轻 比穿孔疼
Less than a bullet, more than a piercing.
很好 完全没有参考价值 谢谢
Great. I have no reference for that. Thank you.
- 早上好 天使们 - 早上好 查理
- Good morning, Angels. - Good morning, Charlie.
埃琳娜 恭喜你
Elena, congratulations.
谢谢查理
Thank you, Charlie.
你准备好了我随时可以开始
All right. I'm ready if you are.
准备好了 给我翅膀吧
Hell, yeah. Give me my wings.